<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">1371</field>
<field name="name">HVC5221</field>
<field name="asr">there came a g. b. grade manager noise and your strength breath the end the year noise the threat is here noise and_he is they're picking up along the side noise he stick a needle and_that side and q. first steps and then you take that needle noise that's the key to to make it like in that noise breath later annulled noise and there you first steps on that needle noise i take care noise you don't pick up your second trapped but just very hard to_see new for me in the slate noise and you put the first needle through noise and you met noise he threw it over noise so in my case i have to pick up fourteen stitches noise down the side and i'll be the third one just to show you noise like i said i like to pick up to you noise so that there's no sort of holy stringing effect noise i think he gets quite tight not picked up three to nit pick up noise fourteen on the side noise and then you go in nato across noise the stench is that you have on and then you get a pickup noise again and then you_have a circle and against their client circles noise so hopefully that makes sense to you noise o. k. so you're going_to end that this way noise down the side noise she's really are worried noise but after you've done a couple times noise you get the get the gist of it so that helps </field>
<field name="ocr">I F 74 w WE r dI 9 Ii hL pp 4s  Wp bi I I1K i F a 1 I Phb F i a4 I vd Fp pp  k 7 pr4 Ie iii a4 vI 4 PUt a 7aJ L a WV A rr7 iI EI 4   pj ii i Y7U T iv hbLjE jr LThN im B WV 7J  I P V E7J  LTY ppju II  mm ph p u rKJ p  haJ V W f F d pw vI Pr K qi 1 rn I   Pdh wT I  E mwI zi jfmI bA ILl  ft J4 j7A V71I KAU vLi F  jq pp L  Ij qw ic7ijJ U if 1 7 ILl pp 1 tj Ze1 mL U hUP1 pI rj  I Id qY WV jwm mL 1 I  U 1b  FY SI iid4 Ld Iy Ibi1 Li Aj 1 ia I LILJ w1 II pII P1 p wrr F KPj P1w iU Lii i K drJ rr 1 wr ryj m  u pI 4i A  ffi I  U EVE 7 mm V7 pw v7 F7 hihLA FW w2 LL S 4 ms wYwww ww Ka F  I W I mmi4 7 WV w4 WY WL  4 Ad ij viz W d Vi ww VC F pJ F Vrrt p e9  w Vii JAhJ I Ji L 7hZI1 p Yis a4J iA Ia 1J vig Fp mPI FYh 11 w4 pr pi wI AFJ 2fl pr Ai JEPj fk i I m  LI LL V6 E E i2 rJ im a 4 54 F U F I VT Fri rTA 1 tI wfrj LI EU W I T1 WV  VA 17A U I iN rA L r4A rA El upli PqvP4 w A wwI r wA rw 5 ii pp1 VuvA Fsd FRfdd r4sd I k Ij FW d rTA P221 p 1 WI1 w4 LD Ik  m4 F  VdSj F 7J 4W bA 7 iA F Uj </field>
</doc>
</add>
