<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">2265</field>
<field name="name">HVC3336</field>
<field name="asr">noise breath and in that case noise mhm noise well all right noise that's just bang manners there are noise noise noise yes it is noise noise there noise noise sure noise that's really what that means it's all part_of it yes noise i do that music coming up on my face again noise i think that noise yeah noise noise noise it also i don't yes indeed noise noise noise or half right pace link that these and other noise wolf why her media degrees whack pretty well noise breath yeah noise all right noise noise from academia and noise the hands of the baltic states noise yes noise noise yeah noise that means they're going_to bring you started this noise case music noise okay noise all breath filler not noise noise okay well you got that you performed even may never a problem with this and trying to train the area that i don't noise i mean noise she said that_he can put it all_right noise c. n. n. and c. i. a. noise let's turn again to hear noise that's right noise let's count ollie is going noise yet harrington rates and i noise this must be and i don't noise noise noise noise music yes sure noise it's it isn't and that's all wrong here noise noise noise music yes noise noise all_right and are you noise you know noise our poll noise noise noise breath and in that case noise mhm noise well all right noise that's just bang manners there are noise noise noise yes it is noise noise there noise noise sure noise that's really what that means it's all part_of it yes noise i do that music coming up on my face again noise i think that noise yeah noise noise noise it also i don't yes indeed noise noise noise or half right pace link that these and other noise wolf why her media degrees whack pretty well noise breath yeah noise all right noise noise from academia and noise the hands of the baltic states noise yes noise noise yeah noise that means they're going_to bring you started this noise case music noise okay noise all breath filler not noise noise okay well you got that you performed even may never a problem with this and trying to train the area that i don't noise i mean noise she said that_he can put it all_right noise c. n. n. and c. i. a. noise let's turn again to hear noise that's right noise let's count ollie is going noise yet harrington rates and i noise this must be and i don't noise noise noise noise music yes sure noise it's it isn't and that's all wrong here noise noise noise music yes noise noise noise breath and in that case noise mhm noise well all right noise that's just bang manners there are noise noise noise yes it is noise noise there noise noise sure noise that's really what that means it's all part_of it yes noise i do that music coming up on my face again noise i think that noise yeah noise noise noise it also i don't yes indeed noise noise noise or half right pace link that these and other noise wolf why her media degrees whack pretty well noise breath yeah noise all right noise noise from academia and noise the hands of the baltic states noise yes noise noise yeah noise that means they're going_to bring you started this noise case music noise okay noise all breath filler not noise noise okay well you got that you performed even may never a problem with this and trying to train the area that i don't noise i mean noise she said that_he can put it all_right noise c. n. n. and c. i. a. noise let's turn again to hear noise that's right noise let's count ollie is going noise yet harrington rates and i noise this must be and i don't noise noise noise noise music yes sure noise it's it isn't and that's all wrong here noise noise noise music yes noise noise all_right and are you noise you know noise our poll noise noise </field>
<field name="ocr">1 1 bIU RNIII I  1 R e kNtii mI p m jTI A w  jmm hfiI mJ  S a w5 173 I L  I I I II  I ll T w  1 I vv 4tYEk rz  e I  7y F7iw mE jrj L7W7  Lm 4 ih mind wb lII 41 I  vWk 7 id I  pj  bPP WI uuI 4hk U a Kr jbJ I idi 7wlawrl guiiJ dE    Sm fF1 pIdJ wq 414 IM a  hi  Il  t1IadJ Lii 4fJ4 4Z Y4  F  F  p   Y I  ah c4bi Tdi rEv F tgIU r1 LTA ah wdnA Iv T  Iw W 1 Yu idMi 4r iw pAid hd AU Fe lm7 I11gd  La Li w1 I F   FL  amA41 Ak wIIriJ 2 w I a ad U k I w  U Up S I  Fhip FI2 ui A Vt a Wd si a b  u 1 rna A  I LJ LU pPr pI rra 4 w1 hL BY U Urn RI  L I WY I  L1i1C p  j  I rY  I 5 4J9I J1I 14 Iiq I 2 L I Ti tL J L J fii Id r44 jib ii i rvi  I M I rv PL 7 Wi ILi rw iii I id VP eiL  94 B  idlE j LJ IIL r4Iy did rvb Ja1 mw rv ii V IAl vY It LP a LI I   l1I L4 U h Ibik 1jq rv iI Im ffa LJ LL bD  1DA mhJ UMe P4  VOL Le k9J v iWahI AWk Ei  U A 4 P19 L1LL mU I WJ  EYpq Lw U P sJul F ILV Iy had A EIILT wJuw rwi I flALLi Wgg   WdhfW V FIEIWJ RI 1 7g wb r I I 1T W4 m     bL Ev I i2f1 F wwv I AbL 4J Ye Y Ye ply m pw h a LLU m 1 A rw rip rW bI mJ 7N L N i a m T  4 I A pw L  K L4q U L U  wEr pgF Iw 1 a I Iv pm 7 FI wIw 4f Ut a V A I WY dJ N  rv k  I  I I rv P dUd am 1 r I II VV izq PEw FEb h7 S bm mm 1WS  LL MV J I ELU I p S  91 a L p p  I vi pv Uaw V A wuq VW if   Igj py uW7 P p    EJ  iv zA 111 U XL rx 1W  UVA 7j w7Ij A U I  II mu RI   VICh 11 Ui ml YUtVb F  IA hLI L2 Jm LAIh 1 IJ Im I gr  ii rn I I QI hV AW Ad   re IJh I Nvi I XCJI 1i V1 I 1 ff ifl I v I  1fIA 1711 ii aE Li 11 ie PS F XIYb ji SW   vuuI  AXN Li 111 I  rr a v1  m IlIl PwJ k4 F pq TPTwiI v Uwdr rA pi 2  im uu 1l j  pa 7 I WAW I L1rU Ii in I ff rfl77  I V II U UAfY PLb 1 Au LAS 15 Iu xxY Ii nil Aq 5 U Wal aI Eww Pr W11 ET  F U j  1 B  L1 Ew I  A L 4 h mmk ummJ I LiY I  L  L W  Lq Lq2 j 3m AI XJ 0U Nil pr bA 4 V2J pv1 LJ A F  WV qd LL w  a  d J1 I1 I1 Lq4  a F1 ii LI  A ma vj I ri VI ri LJ LA F7 CEII LdA hi 1k bm Aj LZ pJ d7J 1J LA iIffU mJ U V d 1 bL4 FE  I LA EI It  Y It J 1I I j jJ I  a fr Tj Li A inAI LJ IJ IIJ AI N fljfljJI LE Ij II H WIY 1 h1 ww  we Fm 1 h mAaj LvA 4C7h1 B  717Am I Wi 4 ir A 4 PPI 1Ti5IM tAC Y4WIA LXJM WT1 Ad WT 4PY7J h 7T rXj wTi I I h  E h 1 P5 WT U 4i k I LFV it PAl Ji V  a I wI IWP Z PT 4  Yh I  i  vI hi fyi vI F wile  hIA 171  Es A  31 LI9 Fd w7 fbd IW II 1 1 iI w71 L p u  vi aPI w1 Lu LT LJI dl  aj Al WT mbd WT wv w7 p 7 Ii qjf uIII wi rT I aiL JI P7TJ I  L1 P1 we A44r1 Iw  </field>
</doc>
</add>
