<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">3145</field>
<field name="name">HVC5495</field>
<field name="asr">noise c. b. s. will adjust noise you saw was the right of the same time noise you also see around me noise and you're sure you saw whatsoever noise i mean it's not the same noise he knows what he's saying see noise the a. b. c. n. n. los off noise see this whole thing noise let's take you live noise i mean the toxins noise of course the silt that any diseases of care noise we'll see what they hear all this time noise yes noise is that life is very serious noise and you look at it noise well it's a case noise see that's the way noise and if so why do you agree it's noise inside c. i. a. noise that's all i do different things that should not be noise yeah noise yeah noise talking about the degree that you have these noise and although it's getting access noise when we put those in sea lions may see noise i did instead of the talks there noise cigarettes that said that the media noise well you know i just said noise well yeah noise yes noise money is so far noise and for me noise onassis' son parts noise and you go outside noise our house noise does the noise we'll see noise he's positive together noise because it's easy to me filler noise in the hearts of three noise these are whole suit pharaoh noise he did it black noise i just noise c. n. n._b._a. says yes noise you did in size slots there as it affects the game noise the smoke from the same as not only path you're right noise and also the day noise but i think today's very units serve all with you noise also you dated about what's the noise try it in school noise also noise the problem noise because the land of oz noise what's the right noise is that i'll see noise i mean losses looking noise hey john noise simon cancers noise i think there is noise the consensus on noise see this little breath this is causing within wanted bad debts noise yeah noise sacked one every five noise yes the united states is slow one noise every year sleeping pills noise two hundred thirty six thousand men noise and one hundred forty two noise all those of these figure early death noise a there's a cancer pneumonia noise judy noise that's right noise i know and and the ideas of syria still open noise no new taxes on it noise those very fast noise stop the majority of americans smoke noise well that there be a_lot more americans noise cigarette smoke noise is the thing almost noise yes noise premature noise every year noise yes noise he is noise cigarette smoking is well it just noise solved in a case here noise see noise </field>
<field name="ocr">flu i1 TI 1 1 1 at Ebh In I II L1U w IEItt AL  k1 if B raw U U AL hL pi 3 5 5 mw pp 3 pp JL JL T1 JL JL AL AL a a hA I h uJ L4J rri ppm Iu Lb Iii1 J7 11 I A A LII 7w mx 1mL AL  J2 Lii pJtiI icn I IL IAL hW I3t gil gil 3T I 1 maiI I yq iri Fzim I q9 4I I7i he u Jh L1 u 1 m5 iqJ ivy AL AL AL 7d 3s 7 pJ LA EIIL 4 Iuu Iuu IUB1S IUB1S I mV3 F LL I tAIL I tiI I I  I La AT A1 7Th k1 1 I  rL EFLS r51 II I5 Lk I s1 7 I I met p rn LI LJ lug La qr1 fir J fflj II j flj fJ1 A ff1 A q A flj rnJ flj A qUj qj qfj qfj qfA qfJ YUj  ii if iJ flj 7fj I1 qj yfj qjj mal qjj qj qj IT 11 A 71 j L 4 71 j II j CA If j CA flj qy1 I C U m  iDOL mwJ A A a mi LI a7 1TT A ir lilA ikL 7A 2 U Ill  I I  I Ij II Ij iflA If I a ii Ij UEL ali WI I Ii I I AL PI I II I j flu TI II  II I j w w Kt IA Icr J  mm 5 I fr1 BELiJ ma in I1Ti U rqI f IiI I Ii NW 35 In mi I1z1j rj A in 1f r kL I I I Ilk I  up F r7j up 1311 A 4j Al 16hI  kU Al rim Lii Lii F L I p 41 nhjA L 1 L LtJ kkA iAhrA LA IkA JI LD 1 1 5 5 1 up iL L1 7wU t1 L U U tAIl 1 F1 I lull 1 p7 r 1 wmm fix JL Iv F vrn I I  Ev ptv9 pw E U 1a4 p7J Wi ii I Lii 3 IF pJ r A C r7 m7s dU if A flu I 51 j i7 if I nt ffJ I La I j IJ j 1 j U j II j 111 j II j II j EAJL A III j I  lL 111 1 71 1 71 1 I j r1 ff1 I Ill I 1111 1 In I In I 1111 1 I j AT Ad 7I 11 1 b j zqu b j  1 pi aIt I I U mqhF IEat 0 A LKA II4 U vsl kK1 LL mBL mBL AL NiL u U L1 mu urn I In urn I mu urn I 0 Falt b4J IjI F 1 1 aOL Em LA 4d 1 1k LIJ1 kMdJ U Lii in 3W a 3W 3W I 3W I  gI If fl Ti A find U ll U BE In PK9 ivy L PU UII lv L La I  IC4 SW 4 4 IJ Ilk Ilk Jr KX I LI ml L1 Ebmb I1j T r A r7  I  1 L2 Inn Ii I u r1ht I5L Ih N p7 1 1 F 11 L 1 I i771 dim AL fl PL  It I Ik41 T7 LI a IK rn I3jL  i1I I3jL I3jL lift hff Iif B V ff mE j1ri in flU 2A rsi La E7J p L2 LI ppw Fpw ppw ppw Fpw Pi ri Wi TTT 4 i e9 w  IhL  21 If i uq 2W 2W A 4q U 4I 3i Fp L7   w lB U 1I jr kI La La KI La La Ip Ih  pru pru  I I w LZ V L7Zd 47 LL rw I A 3 ppw F  in L N L m I z7 ri 1 U A a VP q EvJ rn F r1 T4F E IL L I 4v LL laI RIL wr I srn Il ws 1 1I LU rL Ba Ba w U Ba myI I 1 r1 rb rI nJ 1 ih  Jv1  ddlI EILkL r I JF j  j FKEh I IH 111 1 La LdI LdI 111 I Illj ff1 I JL if In j ni j ni j Ill I Ill I U Ill j U dill j ill j 71 1 1u 171 j 111 I 1TI 1m I in m9fl IaE a 101 I uBtI La ueI I La La La La La La Fill La thU p7 ja IL IL IL IU 11 4 A Al WAhI ix E pI kt  U  U  U FZ 4 A rL7T d1 46 1 U 4 Fp A 1w5 piz LIE 71 vi II I kL II I kL Ifl j kL kL II I kL kL Its j fit j  I Iw j www mBL mBL mBL di hI hI </field>
</doc>
</add>
