<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">3239</field>
<field name="name">HVC5702</field>
<field name="asr">noise there there noise and noise know noise the day and the a. a. is not a low really in the wild now pose breath noise noise there there noise and noise know noise the day and the a. a. is not a low really in the wild now pose breath noise breath noise breath noise it filler noise ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh oh who run the word breath the head then ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh filler breath noise poll breath the election i noise yeah noise noise breath noise </field>
<field name="ocr">d5 II U bI F  p Ewe rt i5 1d 3  ah4 7Ij Vp  I  9j hL 7stc9d rUI Ed H94   Ir2 3uUj C U 3 6is9j 91 PjAL mbI LFL  1 ILa UUJL sSwj b LI rw1a 7 WV L qi ftP0 c1 Er  aI Wsq 4LJ A 7i Ip I iiU ad pp L2 IA Is  fri73 Ag  u T44 gp fr4IP3 A L4A qI J L3 Iz77 hjkfd f1 ILIL kIa LISAI m c7w LI mw Mi p w K9 p j wr mEpp   U ItIi ELia cu fI ppp I zi I I L  J L  L1 I  ml A F77A i  F FEz Wr A IAA I   J I lb e  L  IA 7 1 it g3u  1 bE r m 2 I twI wJ rn Y4 Fr  hr b I I Li mb7 fi F Fij  q F7 4 4y FI i zi pFU ra L1 U Nm  ra I V U WKJ U f p ft sum  2 IN yu Ah IJ I I KqY LTA LJ LfA r7 3  w  IA EILijh WW PLI rfl Lj7 1 hi I 3 di  IIYt 1 E f Ids rn 1 8  I  V  w1iI U   a I WV ftg h1 4 Lf 4 A 11 4I W F stA Ii IFk   3174i 4 wp  rAId idIhd R 2 mNp1I pt4p A  a  mhVrk   ft V  Jj E4C 111 rj Iii WE rye qm B ULIdL 2eCWA hl cliOA 2caO k  iLZl qdeo 7cP2O A d1e7 Lj Awl I AUIIOL 9cO J leCCO caO A 9caO 11 rnrn S   sg 9cdO QedO wewl I AU lION eCeO I77 Vh QedO JJ U IA U 4 I 011 I rwu  0me uu p  1  I 1T r vi kAy I L1 PI 1I   U  7 I LI iOiUDOI OiUDO 10 AID C IONL AL rJ p Yc I fbjj  LOMDO NCh LONDON LOJVOO LONDO LONDI 1ONDO ION lf17 IONDO a UND 0NOo 9 9 9 9 9 9 9 9 9 9 9 9 I 1 Er U C   Yjr ia IZ7 LL IAIJhWA9 7 r1 iE FWWADV Anr 2002 I8Saaro 2003 Chaunpk Joe John ManganejIo Bacak ess 2006 ritest uon AnuiaI Walk Passaro ha mu 5u5J I John wan Mai BOigUIipI 2000 55 Wa Dc Champion 2006 sm ouan Ray Aim 2002 Sgaro 2003 Champion JOfln Bac Co 2006 ITS as UjUO mo 2002 Passaro 2003 nrual 20Q4 wiiii John Caige LLU 2006 6 6 anuftnE Ray m0o Cobon K srbjUan WardV II1I 2002 asSro 2003 2004 ial w IlUs Cnt Eati fbi Joe John Pagi 1Ude 6e ao92006 era hrbuUon ay eWo Ccban Dept Wmrd 2002 SSSero 2004 w iii uai John Joo e 8j 2007 I nI I Pmw ruello JWm  Warci A 2002 ISSWO 200s 2004 opL Dc John Joe Pj 2007 2006 ITS wv 0PrSUOn Ward v 2002 20O 2004 Dpt Fat Va Iu John pa 2007 2006 ITS Pss r 1 LVA r 1  Et J  PTa P7i IA quj b N El I rm sI rdrn II B  IIIJ I pp l I v 5 UzFqFij 1  I I I J iimI t LII 1  mibi ill Iq F WgI p IYY 757 I  I1 f  f   di INU jiMI m jq 4I V mIIJ U ER U E FR LI  I I I I aff II I d  4 i I j U II  I pF U 1LRLIUJ </field>
</doc>
</add>
