<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">3898</field>
<field name="name">HVC085445</field>
<field name="asr">there are one in one city official old west ryan for missions fund raiser noise noise experience was not at all and you were there already noise on this so much you think or what what's the noise see partnership what should come in through this breath so here we are and he should've offspring and burners show national institution where i was a half by law music pat let_me just music see you back noise into a shell from the time noise thank you for supporting noise one shuffling are commissioner music yeah music breath ted breath and so on and aid and aware and i'd love you all music breath well noise music noise well noise yeah noise music yeah that's all right music to know music i said music yes noise and music the jurors are highly reliable all me and then noise the noise noise noise are noise these are all on the music yeah music what i am someone who is in that music noise music noise music you know music yeah music i don't know music thank you all music breath filler noise music bad girls music we're saying music breath i want_to risk losing jobs music in the right music noise and got to regroup music noise wow music not really good job on dole music yeah music o. k. music but jay music we'll be back right music yeah music noise filler noise music yeah music to do that music noise music c. n. n. music well well i don't know what noise music noise noise noise </field>
<field name="ocr">bI UL I  mZ I  bd IL 3  I  mZ IPhL I  4 Jp rg L4 E5 I WY Fr   El 9 1 4 tiiIj I  14 J3 up U KI It Jaki 9911 aJ W7Y UJTO uT IrE U fLiii 1r jflLi WriI FJFU fli vrAfL err II RU i I   Ln  Eli aJ In 3 II LLt IIILLI I AI KYI WI wYw Ird wY wYw 4i  It  II I j Lr bia wYYY I KWI Ii a II 4 IIhU  4 I I III pa I  pI 3dI   LAI a iAp mI 7r I ua ia pa iif ai id MI 5161 Ut Ii WI 9 v wJy 1WU Pu L4JKU 11 4 ii   je U II 74i r  rig  5 Ld F U    IiU  L bUd py p7 WI W7 FL L r  U rTnm mu w LJ Lx d mim3 we WV KhC  U V L 41 Fi i qy P A ww Ijw rw iIh rrx ri inK W w2  rId i riiq T7 mmEmjeI pq U Je ry TLU WK FIB K  4P K a  w  7I mImbl wp t4h U LI wwJ  JiM vi 6L I i1 1 13 flu VAi Ii VIi LA4 2U v Li I L9 ai d www Wi hL4i di aIy IaIh b rr um w  U FA 1 r  jj IAUI id  m awl 1TJ 2I fr Pr bIL I lEA 1  y 7z rn IRq pm wvE U KZ bWP Imbm qabad r hm ffia 7  juj fiJ tik AN ifli L1 W 4 A Li Eb p 4 IfIi  It I jJ y47m wU if mm W7 Rubbing  AIAh RubbiflAIjj RubbiNAIJI Ru bj1coho I RubbgiIcohoI j Rubbi jIcohoI  bu RubbicohoI  Rubbing4cohol j 5il RubbingIcohoI Ru bb in iAIc oIiillJ Rubbing Al  iJJJ Rubbing Rubbing I I S ULi1 JJ Rubbi  UJ1JJJ JJJ4JAJiJJJ Rubbing Alcohol Rubbing Alcohol Rubbing Alcohol Rubbing Alcohol Rubbing Alcohol Rubbing Rubbing Alcohol Rubbing Alcohol hal Rubbing Alcohol RubI1i AizujiJ jJJiJJJ Jk JJ JziiwJ Rubbing Alcohol JJ4J JzjwJ wJ IZLJJJ4JJ Rubbing Alcohol 11 Rub jJjAizuJJJ Rub Rubbing Alcohol Alcohol Rubbing1cohaI  Rubbing Alcohol Rubbing Alcohol Rubbing Alcohol Rubbing Alcohol 2 Rubbing Alcohol F IbiiLI vi Irni ru vi 17 </field>
</doc>
</add>
