<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">3915</field>
<field name="name">HVC087202</field>
<field name="asr">noise breath oh noise noise little noise breath noise noise filler well noise breath filler noise what you need cheney noise breath no more potent and all i can noise they noise the noise breath noise and filler in filler noise noise will i noise noise breath and polls can noise and noise breath noise the noise all noise and filler noise the noise oh yeah noise the e. e. o. of_the women and i want to know what and love the the the noise one little been burned there breath filler are filler noise filler breath music noise breath noise filler noise it noise bob rubin the head wound from all these noise and filler that noise music yeah music breath no and noise breath she noise filler and music noise okay noise music i mean he said o. k. let's go to your noise noise noise what noise what noise noise little noise breath music oh sure it's an odd way or another car breath and here in the noise filler noise filler breath filler and music noise it's noise music the s. and that's it for all of_this is how the past music noise music i think breath all right music breath well filler yeah noise music noise well noise music noise music noise music noise music noise music noise music noise music you mean the people who breath filler why noise hello breath music what do you know </field>
<field name="ocr">IL IWi wa Nx 5 I Ar 21 F1 II wz LAL 1 I I DIBX I 9  iK I wild 1 7  1 Lvd a w mmm 1 F V 4 Jad 1fri 1 4 I  Lrf1 AJ w  a L 1p a K 4 B 1 ti 1W a I4PL Lj 7i 1 V I a 1 7LN I i a tjdi1 1 vi I hi Fe  I  La b d p1I 1  LAiII rww Li r  F F ri1 It 94 m Lu  b1 4 I I WV 1 rj qgq V id I wpw  Fr W 4 I Up LI 1 Lh3J F J3LPA K r  JJ 1 1 VI ZM wI 1 4 Ii rThIk 1 p IwM r   N pw F 0 E I L I LIZ III h4 I ml PS ES rru IC 121 M1 VJ 9 FdW rf M FZ Lam if ww bAnd did Fr qA F I Kip p w s4 WE V  hI 21 L31 7 J Jn i 5ffL LLAI WV PR I Eq em AI Ii p ziI F EL J I 1j WV F 44 iJLW 1 IEME7 1LMJrrj f7s jU4V AovJ CLL7 WJL jAoJ OcMLWflt tr1v WJL AnW D4bILAJI1Y WJL jqAJ AJ D1LTT7 4c cwrt7 tc1s c7 VJL Cr1y rv WJL IdE j4J CO1LbIJY WLJ4V ClLhiJfIl fJI kOAJ 5o1tJ 4LJW wit jLJJ 3k4JrW LAflAJ WJLJ 5oAJ t41s rdE Irc jLj4dJ cI orW  VJL j44J Ck91LhiJrW Qo1LWW 1dC 5AoAJ filE crT7 wit rdC 4 V 23 I I 1 A j lwt Ii q1 II ry 4 iJsI 1 4 KI 5 LZ v1 wlLgfr 9 4a LL V24LcL I L4 YA LAU Vh I F U liz I   Tidki4 1 k I   y I1 h77 V VJU cp a It Ab p 8 4 Iq ki2J F Liii T A AWE Ls34 I Iv1 I w  I F I u  U J  m p4 YirzLs I IikL I 1 FL LILA i 1 7 i ii lilA Iv W4i fl T4 3 i4U Eta F vi Iii ru FrY LI Li UtIJ iI ir mis  LU V2 LiI II  rLl Th 1  WfFWJI A Lz 9A  E by I ILl iUI prs wJ 7fr IA F F w A hA w   zr UU f LikA iii Ik 44 p tx 4 W a Ldl Lv wa  I  w1 a 44 U F L WJ9 KAUi III qi WV P q w i LA4  vv wq wwu </field>
</doc>
</add>
