<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">4197</field>
<field name="name">HVC132187</field>
<field name="asr">if you visit any n. c. l._a. facility breath and yet like training facility where there's some serious trading going on in a cross that box you know it's a commonality noise and that is olympic lifting platforms that's those big strips of waiting on which the letter stant surrounded by robber workplace could drop noise it also noticed a_lot of different colored place people barbara plates noise and there the need to be dropped from not varying heights noise the reason we use these kind_of place is that if you didn't olympic left like a queen a juror to snatch from which we can drop us a myriad of i was like benefit the safest thing you can do while performing these lists as chop away oftentimes you voice await using a cleaner and gerry there's not rental we're header shoulder level but you wouldn't normally be able to handle to say this we lower this back down the gun again is just to let a drop in and guide the top of the bar with an open palm most gyms front is going_to be eighty now because because against a business model not because it's an unsafe left you know you can only see this kind of weight lifting on television now during the olympics it's still very common for development powering football hockey noise in other hip dawn in sports this was the original form we're looking proctor spy decrease and then down in mass trauma competitions all the way up until the late eighteen hundreds he's the less that noise not gyms like wyan c. a. was built on noise and now you can find in most years in fact people come in for our basic scores and the how the drop awaits from over and just get used to it they usually timid not because they're scared but because the cup practices soul commonly band but they're worried about making noise the survey and other people noise a startling people that's a </field>
<field name="ocr">ILJL 3 1 pyu IL 4 Eu IL iu Li I1i II I LLi FL7 C5 PILL AE w m  tWi L1 iiu lbJAm LP4  U As  ILl L jsq jL I fj IhI iA u I TI tL 1 La El I Aq Ik 11L vI  Pu U I  F I LO Ih 2L xJ I LI 1I Em Eu3 aJiFY U WwT ILu LI jaumEwi LAy h r z if L7 L Li 7c EEi  I  r 4 A  iN s Lv w pj A  Y4q1I Ij jq tWa wq i1e F I 93pq ypp w  3 IJ a   S a a IT 5p15UZ i EN Ugh L mril zii WY I I h Ji LY Id 5gJ kI LJ U J up AM 4 U 11 ItA LLLX1 41 1 wp EN y rc Ww q Ii JL LLLA J  I U K I I I MLL pull Ju b4 I I vd kL Z91 YPhi La bp LA L LEX q1W L4 L4 IlU E5 rz r4 AFk Ci 4EJ 1 U EB EIE EIz Egq Iil h  Ia pJI uII 1 LI J7y A iFT4 wa j57j 4 i1 u j LAI TII I bqbV L U leA IA p3 haL IA Yu LJ 1 b a vi I 59 iii Iw ma mJ TEl mJI mJ F q7 19 I j Lu L A fN 7 iqwI V NrE  rLIJ LaL U LLI ap qp 7badL Eh imp mh 4 L armt I I r1ibma EEx1 L1 F ii iIShI LI I9II U 91L I I ru pz1 II LI a a 4 wj 9 wJ EL nu uu wi nu Ma  3  I a ma  mi tu pi eb II LJ 1W inZI pj </field>
</doc>
</add>
