<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">4300</field>
<field name="name">HVC158642</field>
<field name="asr">noise ice cube came back in another we can project in the pages of nature magazine breath if you're one of the thirty three million plus happy owners of it by phone noise you may also have been one who has suffered a catastrophic events noise well cracked eye phones screen breath while there's no reason to panic because for about thirty dollars you can replace as eye phones playing and i show you now attorneys we can broaden his eleven music word on the twenty two is where you'll find the breath i_have full screen repair project by morton's globally in addition to your cracked by phone three or three g. s. breath you're going_to need the touch screen replacement some front panel that he's of strips and a few other things you'll find a link to breath on this video and along with this posted where you can buy them to begin with you want_to pull out your sim card so use a paper clip to do that breath and then you can do is to screws and the very bottom of the full those two little tiny screws need to come out noise and a_little trick is to grab a magnet to hold these teeny tiny screws because you don't want to lose them using an exact tonight for very small screwdriver you want_to begin by prying the screen assembly away from the case use caution not to cut the rubber molding because between the screen and the case after a little bit of work to screen assembly will be freed up noise breath in you'll notice it's pretty ridden cables at the very top of the full those need to be disconnected now d. l. c. d. panel needs to be removed from the screen so there's some screws breath the total of five side screws and then there's one lonely little screw breath that's breath on the inside it needs to come down as well noise once all the screws are out people c. d. assembly will come clear of from the frame there noise noise don't let information overload you can find what you need the town out of reach you probably heard the news i was smart and from my side topic and get it noise and i get it noise breath this next step is the most tedious and time consuming because you have to use great care breath using a heap done and again an exact tonight for other small object breath we're going to be separating the screen for the screen frame breath it can be careful don't notice because you don't want_to damage the frame that the screen is attached to it when you're all done on the screen will come free from the frame be sure to check for any breath cracked blasted might still be stuck to it they're using some rubbing alcohol in the q. tip noise breath clean afraid really well and you may even have to use exact tonight to get some of that breath it he's of all off breath because we're going_to be replacing it breath with these pre cut panel it he's of strips there be two strips one for the top and one for the bottom breath so put those in place carefully and when they're down a good answer cure breath remove the protective cover now it's time to take you replacement screen breath and put that in place starting at the bottom of the phone breath in slowly you laid in place making sure that it fits nice and tight became full about what those ridden cables get in the way because they need to be plucked did and now it's time to reverse that this is some lee process so we're going to put the l. c. d. breath assembly in place breath attach the screws for that and then re insert the three ridden tables in the base of the phone and snap your n. by phone to screen assembly in place and you just replaced your cracked screen on your i've phone we'll see you next time with another weekend projects noise and so noise just breath noise it's noise noise </field>
<field name="ocr">E U U wwwE 66 E U U wwwE 66 E U U wwwE 66 E U U wwwE 66 E U U riecoi S  wwwE Ideo riecoi wwwE Ideo riecoi wwwE Ideo LdJ Ii   fh fl3 wwwE Ideo riecoi wwwE Ideo riecoi wwwE Ideo riecoi wwwE Ideo LdJ riecoi wwwE Ideo riecoi wwwE Ideo EcoI wwwE Ideo EcoI wwwE Ideo ii  fh fl wwwE Ideo EcoI wwwE Ideo ii  fh fl wwwE Ideo ii  fh fl wwwE Ideo ii  fh fl wwwE EcoI wwwE Ideo EcoI wwwE Ideo EcoI wwwE Ideo ii  fh fl wwwE Ideo EcoI wwwE Ideo EcoI wwwE Ideo ii  fh fl wwwE Ideo EcoI wwwE Ideo ii  fh fl wwwE EcoI wwwE ideo riecoi wwwE ideo riecoi wwwE ideo riecoi wwwE ideo riecoi wwwE ideo riecoi wwwE ideo riecoi www Video Li3J FLH F p y JYp1 I r  lily1 kii VA 7  7 h rJIJ rJI Tjfv Tjfv Tjfv Tjfv I I I FLivi Ffk1 mxz Ki FLW1 L  Lw IAJ I I IqJ Ffk1 wJfvjx ii wJfvjx iz A Ip I rfk FIfVr K7 IJfj fJfYi FJjfVbv VA II4fvj KY I FJfj   Fik1 ILbI ILbI ILbI ui1 VIEW I 2 P VI4FVI Jfy A jiW  V i pr j 4 Fr 1 ra pr  4 4 TI ii W d I  Al FJf Ix Iii L 4 I iILU TJY ErI rawii ii LiJ jqv Ja mis  v ad S I rn  WA  p ej h Ii  Phoi Phoi Phoi Phoi Phoi Phoi prn  N LAT p NW Pr   Fp Jt4y Tusdev 41 Jy Ju July 1 AEqi KiL Tuesday Jy Tugsm Dsdv Pd N   us Tusggm MVID ra tusmgmv I W T   AI a Iqj 19   U  d  T hi  Tuss 8U NS4 SO  sU  1usedey vi   LI      p  Ii 4p ruj U J A w  a rc ww il Li I I ITh6  41A 1 L wt hM  1 UI1I d   ii p1  r tiVdi  b I I qaiI 4Z U U hLA p IE  a M U U U r1 I   I U a L  JpwJ U U Sd LTiL LI  1 K  wh W a Es 7 LU mu I  7 I  77 W7 77 pIwv 7 7 I i Wj LaU B ffi ii 1 Ki Ki B EiJ I Bi rn Iii K V  ELi urn 1I EIIL I 1 LaJ LJJ LJ w  ZI IL I t1 III frmw A  A  AlL I 4 IxI ru F Leiui LT I 4h uimhd L7 7q r II 4 iJL 0i A11 AJ0 hIA C A4 tJtu 7W AJO Em K 11Al tJe AJCr I tJA ASC rTif I RU A j 7W I71f  AJcY 6 11 tj AI6u t I 77AAJ Jtu 1 77A AJcY Af9 fJE6c 7A AJc7Y AY61 7 cZ 1eW1 AIIAJ A CU  9IVJA 6 FI6AJ 11 AYAL FE   I bSL9 if IAUF wu pI VW  vi F lid  I  zd it New ivesci iartpcn New iartpcn Nv iartpcn Nv iartpcn Nv iartpcn Nv iartpcn 4 Nv iartpcn 4 Nv iartpcn 4 New iartpcn 4 New ivesci iartpcn 4 New ivesci iartpcn 4 New ivesci iartpcn New ivesci iartpcn Edt New ivesci iartpcn Edt New ivesci iartpcn Edt New ivesci iartpcn Edt New ivesci iartpcn Edt New ivesci iartpcn Edt 4 Nv iartpcn Edt 4 Nv 7eA iartpcn 4 Nv iartpcn 4 Nv iartpcn 4 Nv iartpcn 4 Nv iartpcn 4 Nv iartpcn 4 Nv 7PA iartpcn Nv 7PA iartpcn New 7PA iartpcn New ivesci 7PA iartpcn Itm Nv 7PA iartpcn New ivesot 9e iartpcn New ivesot 9e iartpcn New ivesot 9e iartpcn New ivesot 9e iartpcn New ivesot 9e iartpcn New ivesot 9e iartpcn New ivesot 9e iartpcn Ncv 1artpci New iartpen Nw iveso 1artpc4 hik v V dL S I L t L t 1 U A WT5FPYI wE KJ AdP LI r1J L 1 17 mhY AI i4 aU a JrJ LW  bVW i iA aid L1 Ad M1 tr u WI hu ry v  y Aif iii p1 IJz I 9Id IL r Ja F I LUIId w4i L  wp Eq 4 4q L1 F Phj 7L MItL Ih  1 uv I 21d p Li LNJ LW  J Wi U h Iu Eu di dL p Li Z eIe Kill4 fY EJ21 Y U I1 II vJ Tvu Tvu Tvu Tvu rw ttw I  F7Y 1ff ww wr wmm 1  aEahhl U 1 Lei 1 wu pp U L1 1 D bL I L7 rI L1 mi rI I41i Fr wa WY LI w  I4 I  1W k ii h1 L p If 1 114 E7iA VfcIL hE pf I g 4 w w 41iIea pir nA  i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i i Th Th jq wwwE wwwE ideo E U U ii    flu wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo wwwE Ideo wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE Ideo E U U wwwE 66 E U U wwwE 66 E U U wwwE 66 E U U wwwE 66 E U U wwwE 66 LAT p NW Pr   P NW 2bQI NW NW p NW I  E   dI NW p I  9 0 0 K a p NW easoV P NW S   ciE P NW ciE S eQSo2 or0 eQSo2 eQaSo2 IN NW eQaso 1N eQaso 2 eQSo oc 2 og ow  cww2Qi j  NW cre 3 NW cre 3  NW Is0 LI  a ew  Lk U I 5 Vtin 71 I I Jib 1bsqua Ddy  ri JUbV 4 July July U Ju11 July JUI </field>
</doc>
</add>
