<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">4504</field>
<field name="name">HVC190622</field>
<field name="asr">i mean i removed the her meter that cracking the tide or blacks and to find the crack use moses and i said yeah institution should be handled yelling road burn noise thanks for a show in town noise and in three different thing right and we think that we had and often time well i think i know i remember yeah go ahead and have a whole of the d. e. a. the big day began at what we think he is throwback to shore and the corridor of breath our entry hotel yeah i'd come out and breath noise noise virtually and picking up on breath filler make it work she looks she tours knows susan i know he's really talent ranging thing that i really noise noise what they did not do very well noise okay the the i don't even care what breath filler breath noise old thinking roll her if_you don't know filler and they are breath and filler i'm sure i i noise if_you weren't street today therapy louis it was you know with that you_want_to write anything you're being bashed will be the most non tomorrow we are noise well noise what noise high out there are people breath but which you don't know the shoe is something that i don't think the fact that dole knew of the well we're going_to_have it breath to actually prodded think pre internet for the empire state building here what haley she's there well noise o. k. noise that raid there weren't friends noise if the empire state building noise breath from orlando noise then we're safer we're turning off there the day tomorrow noise where noise </field>
<field name="ocr">F  upa IaJ r4 iri iJ I  I j9 IIb7 LLJ 4bj F7 I bY I a IAjq I A U Lii U a IL I J1 I I F W I UI 21 mfl f Iwi N ft Ad I q III I mpI jrj rn Imii rw mm  I Fc 9 4U1 I  r TII FJ ubJ F 7 i  IEJI 4EhI U WV pwg II ill 81a IJ LfI Pr IJ 4 Ad 1Pf ii ii 1I 7 WI F Id L4d F W r r 11W II LIW 1Jwf IwYI fp I Elm 1d5 ub4 bJ A I L7q IL hg 4 W1 I F Lq mu C 1 I  4pp  53 ru F 1 um 1 w4J k or 11d 7 rF rrj 0 z21 U fEp Frd 2 2p U I pi I I I INc </field>
</doc>
</add>
