<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">501</field>
<field name="name">HVC3219</field>
<field name="asr">noise did there noise the mike i'll do_it noise well sure noise he played directly in the direction of the bar noise well noise first you know i don't hear that last road noise o. k. noise you_want_to make a lot noise joe ben noise you want_to go down hoped noise you can't even astro know want to go right over that noise you go down there about a mile mile and a half noise breath there could be a speed limit died noise yes noise if you don't read that noise all_right noise breath once you get to that point there's going_to be a little field you know on the fact breath noise so you're saying is we're going_to be a deal noise you know you're going_to pass it in and we can build up and you know i keep going beyond that you will noise no no one was trying to read noise well you know if we are magically going all_right noise and_i want to write noise that country noise yeah noise yeah that's right noise but then after that noise they're going_to be somewhat coming traffic noise well that contrary passes he will make a left noise the man of peace there noise there we speed limits and you come up to you noise the sign reads fifty miles an hour noise okay noise o. k. noise o. k. jill noise the ellis island noise you'll continue straight noise joe noise it may be making the right noise going down the road noise after the couple building noise and there it is noise and then we get there noise you know we had to do that but by the bar noise the fight as well are you down noise tell me go to the planet noise yes noise indeed noise the place brings back memories noise good luck to you there noise thank you noise noise yeah </field>
<field name="ocr">IJi Afl zt IA 4 Li if dip ff1 JIA 71A4 71A4 7 7 U P7 Ij  9 4 hIAh Li aXW dhI m  U q   a b a F Ad 7 St  IL a d L FI I ddt U  d Ij LL Iu  FAi d 1 f 1 II IM  U It4 IwIL     jv I  YYYq hLk ILl J  EI I   1  I I U ti fp 4TI v7 IN mM  4A II  U LZI A  L 4r 4  mJ g I b    d rw  L bI Ts   LAd 4 r4I  4 s   pqY Is LI 4 FA p  IIi   IiI MIILhib I i4 8  I1 I mUL pj pp Pr 1k4 iiI ILk ELA all IA 79 Li P R  4 41 4 I t1tIWB 41 jJFF Lv L I 4w 7J D N IrL4 14f jb t p LI bAA 74 Wj4jF  ILL  1ff LL KiLb  LL 01MB a JWf ILL 7j LiL U Iu Yq DVMB I1 Iwj d     Ist dp4 ru III JI pv 71 rw a  a  w KL L  9 A I LI 9  a I uU 4 ii1v   miiI 8tsa LJwa 4 AILh QiMa U 7  b  i 1Iq QUMB 7 1JMB si 011MB  v QIJMB i i4 V iEI IIi di  a  4 tj IIAv 1 LAh s ILA LA jp B pEEs rt I La J zi LJLL fr 4P4 I iLLi FE VVA Al a LAl 4 ILLJ LLii iiuiF 4 b lid g   L Li LA w t LIM8 hsA pV a Ibu 1 OIJM lxii DUMB rwI f5 v   LA AA 4E APU 4 ra L Iu 4 wi U  W Ii wf LkJ 0UR vi U UM 7I IEEb I J F 1IU U OUR S 4 ips I e Ob U  e A A 0 Aft 9  e A 9 A  SD Dt AtI p  7 1  Pu AD i V 1 A 4U OCiW El N  J 4U iMP C A w  t dt VA Wi j 1bLi R L p pi pN d7r LA L  S  rLv iII 1 LL II  1 LAm Lea kL r1 g3 1 OVA Li IJ A 1 jv WU U h1 upI 4mJJ 1 1 UIXIEL w YA w LJJ UN A jqP S I 42 4 LA 1t tJ a  VJ U4 Ma km L7 flhl1 LL dz a N AZ I  I AF 1 Of p1 7 t  8 L4i w    a OLJ a4p 44 nuIe LL flUM 4 hmb LihL nua iL DLA  1 4 cuj 4  w L4h Ff hm IL Ldm OUfL LKq  I OUAY 1  LIJ  1 I uk E LLJ  I4 IJImJJ V 4A LICU  cp4 4L4bmb AV Er Wi EY Em 2 aF tA dl ILh 1 LhL m  rj V  wp s4 Ldh uIJ lv r F 1 I LIJ LLL LlJ IC 5Y  LLii t5 El L 42   v LIJ szLlJ JM15 I 4 Lb  S 4 m pa   F  J IIML Lb LL 7j I  I I 5p  p S  Ib1 U 7J I A2 I  r VAV I    1 h1  St c 2W is   8d EL  I Lii Lin L LL1 a tW 4W aUK a LLhI IJMS 1 El 1 IAr hJ  RIym 5 s A4 4 UALJ vj A 7YZt4 jwyjjj7 U a Ad I 79W vc EF IuIm  pmb 7v vaA ii dAIs 4Sb F  1 IB 4 hd L A WE LkJ Era r 7 I  kJ VA I  mv LkJ ru   E52   LL7  A DL1 JL 1JM8 IMB ii hi  I 9Me L L JM8 I  g FMII  1 LL YbJ 4 4 4 L 9 hhiTJ I IALI rA flW8 pms xLqqm  p k S A Lk haa tg v liMp I  La Ld MB Idm 7 I EJMn L I qiq 4  4L1 PJM8 m7dL PJPfe 9 cx IM9 APb Xzi I1i  Jfqp   I I Ju 4ma Jrit iF a LT ELi Se I Ic Lh LALL wu 4 L JLhbb LLL LAi  V vw PWR I  JE3 iLhb AIJ Pum mjjI MUI 1  Li MILb Wa  Y kI 4jJJJ vJM1 iAi IIL41 hJ4 fw a I I I ii LiihLJ1 I pi hFK dkL h ftWIA mu0 L1 am LiEL1 L1 LMIA ue5 F  P V 3 a I  1I  I  t1mLL iiKiii SE I  alMbJi 7i b g LdLJ    4g SL Iw e ru IlI  LA1 IF4 Iv </field>
</doc>
</add>
