<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">5156</field>
<field name="name">HVC332779</field>
<field name="asr">noise it's not noise breath well the a. a. in dallas then no i noise not noise music noise music would that not a bad man not clean music noise yeah breath music noise music noise the noise music bob there's a high holy day music noise music noise music noise music noise music and in this hall music noise music noise music noise music noise noise it's not noise breath well the a. a. in dallas then no i noise not noise music noise music would that not a bad man not clean music noise yeah breath music noise music noise the noise music bob there's a high holy day music noise music noise music noise music noise music and in this hall music noise music noise music noise music noise music okay music noise music noise music noise music noise music noise music noise music i mean they go back noise music i agree music my noise music noise music </field>
<field name="ocr">all riD At qq p  4 I Yb I  Vrt 5 P U F N 4   7 IJj MJ   btS JppF d A  LA U F 1 I WA FI p AX vE F Iu  f I 5 IgUP 11  1Ijw 7 v1 9 1u K 71  rYa 78  7 M A  t   a w  iia r LI 3 iLij St 4 44  pfJ r AM lb  ii7 ba  JLL4 L V4JhA I4 a l pv   ft s  JN I 1r1A S Ill VIII wj gIt b b 4q imI 4fr Dr w  IAAJ to  qIpj lilt AL ih fr  aAIZFM V Ii V SI LL F  v4 v4 q7 1 5 t I d  m dt pyt I E  7I 1DM bD  4 1 41 1w II 11 gA Ih q L r  Sd 4ej  4d ppEi t1  rAI m7 Ir  FiLJ eta AI 1   Iw qyfl p pw b 9 a as Ld Au   4 bW qy abA Uv y4 9 t I ginA 0 41  4 I   ed iq rev FC 4   w  m1 wEIi Wjiib  WT f9 19 eb FWk mm 44r 4rJr hJ4 wp 2 WE jul a eb wa hd Ir   p a a FF2 aid pmp v J U U IA1 3 piIII p Ie hm PEl w  RI q 1 p aU 1 I 5 auJ U ir ir p  6 p  EZ vuJ uj 3 LL U q 1p  I IhR 4Wgg pm  4 Sf  LL d Ja FL  L7 2q cvJ 4 mmp5   if uI EhbA p  vL h 4 1 w1 S 4 9h b w A 9 a7 rtl 1I bYP w  hLi pm i4 h a  V  U I Yb 4j wgu WI Ir1 r I a  I 4 WE LY 8vP ti j4 ja II F  W7 I U 1 I1 mL 4 iL 4 i L  7w 1t4p Iua I  Ii pY i U gbA 1 41 7T3U ppi 11 fl  AKJd a9 b 4 9 tt u1y4 K  iU Jb  AI LII 8 U U  gj iD 1ff Idmr W 3p IIb Ii  I  1 Yuu ElI Mr 1 ki 4 I  2IU Ve vt   JV I 4qf thAi a   qg J w p 47P  F uMA  iMi  A Ti K 7uu ii   1v rLi Lr 7u </field>
</doc>
</add>
