<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">5573</field>
<field name="name">HVC416954</field>
<field name="asr">music yeah o. k. noise noise filler breath music breath yeah the jews noise music noise yeah breath two music noise noise music yeah music noise music breath noise noise hi noise how and that noise music noise music noise noise music hello noise music noise breath noise noise noise noise now wait noise music noise music good music noise noise yeah noise yeah noise yeah noise music noise music o. k. music noise music noise on the bonds and think about this noise just the right noise music breath yeah yeah noise yeah music noise music noise noise music noise music noise music noise noise sure noise yeah noise music noise breath more noise filler noise music noise yeah noise mhm noise music noise yeah music noise noise music noise music noise music i think music noise noise noise i am music noise music noise music noise music noise music noise music noise music breath noise noise noise noise and music noise music noise well noise breath noise noise noise noise mhm breath noise noise filler these noise and that was pretty at stake noise well done nice work pollution noise what honey noise c. n. n. atlanta noise frank noise that's true yeah noise how are you saying noise noise would you say noise noise noise noise great noise noise filler filler breath who filler breath filler breath noise noise noise noise noise noise noise noise noise noise i mean that and she are noise noise noise noise noise noise noise noise noise how are you sure noise how are we noise breath give up noise breath in her clean your aren't paying any attention to me i_am noise but as c. n. n. music noise noise i don't think noise mhm noise and we breath noise music yeah noise yeah noise noise noise music yeah o. k. noise noise filler breath music breath yeah the jews noise music noise yeah breath two music noise noise music yeah music noise music breath noise noise hi noise how and that noise music noise music noise noise music hello noise music noise breath noise noise noise noise now wait noise music noise music good music noise noise yeah noise yeah noise yeah noise music noise music o. k. music noise music noise on the bonds and think about this noise just the right noise music breath yeah yeah noise yeah music noise music noise noise music noise music noise music noise noise sure noise yeah noise music noise breath more noise filler noise music noise yeah noise mhm noise music noise yeah music noise noise music noise music noise music i think music noise noise noise i am music noise music noise music noise music noise music noise music noise music breath noise noise noise noise and music noise music noise well noise breath noise noise noise noise mhm breath noise noise filler these noise and that was pretty at stake noise well done nice work pollution noise what honey noise c. n. n. atlanta noise frank noise that's true yeah noise how are you saying noise noise would you say noise noise noise noise great noise noise filler filler breath who filler breath filler breath noise noise noise noise noise noise noise noise noise noise i mean that and she are noise noise noise noise noise noise noise noise noise how are you sure noise how are we noise breath give up noise breath in her clean your aren't paying any attention to me i_am noise but as c. n. n. music noise noise i don't think noise mhm noise and we breath noise music yeah noise yeah noise noise noise </field>
<field name="ocr">Mqw R  9U  1 3L dip A2 I WNtI 34  LYU Aji WI ww1 ib pvq 9 VUVI I I    4i w  vI 1 I m7rq v vi pr WHEW F WHEW fry VI vi tv LqI  L9E 4j alma Jp t4 ma   W rt  a I a1  a d 3Er F 9 hiJ wpw mm mtAA iii ma U  vYr rL I1 I VI I W1 IV hhJ frv IA IA I i 1 Len 1LU  Ii 1 ci LF I  4 px Ci   U  hb pUJe h1 a a r  am I  a a4 r2iL  a a4 a 4 a4 mmml tI P4W p j vf1 ii I IL dI If U II Iv a4 I 7j ill I ci I   hb a 4 gI dI I wIYp  I I b S dI I I I 04 vv I   dI 6 I iIz ElU  hb Ld  a jJ Ld I  II vi   f7 hhE  I I   3 L z 7 L a I I I i j I rU 41fT I    id Id LI I f  S I 01 I f iL    ffIfII V  4a dl   A 3 I I iii7 B4 I  2 LE  SI VI VI IE 12 vi I hhL7N VI wt   Tq3i A i  Iw  vi I  VIA V2 VI Vi   P413 A IIu A4q I P3 Vh VtA 11w Pi w  mbI WE 3V tiq vi wu P bAidi hjji4 Yw 4g vI I w u  9YRhW  P iTftf117 ffiLJ 4iv Iw p 2 VI  L  1 b bU pPr IIiIh qp 1 ii 1 Y I  hu frih L  II I  Pp a wuw jj EW 1 AiiW  w MW 2 L7 rv WiESL Xh LYU  t  p   3 I rw hr VI wYww 1 0j M mk U vi r  fdS I I 5 w 1  3 I 3 1  w  vI  4 ild if  7W 4  w ij Si t dAd VI U 4  4 vi VI p7 hTi if  w1 4343 t1J pi w w  Iw C Wi Iw  w I a a VI It1 mu iL 3 3 Vi Iuw 7y I WY rau VI  hAi 4 Ir  3 FW p wi   qw  vIf I 1  4 I  y 14i vi  itl vi im I U Jiamid El I mh mm Jid IE 4j LUE 2 4 41i 4 WI iir 7bhi il A 1 1 VI PFmdN E  R  l A I p I U rnc aIi hb ci tE I hi b4 I m m 3 up t J 1 t igqPq I ci 0 I I I I dI I if I F7 Li I  If  I LP VI  I vI I IA VI bi a4 Ii mumu V I S4 SI dhd1 aI I I V  I 57  vv  1 ihbLbI   Ej If   I a4 I U 2 VI VI S yf  J3  vf iI LJR  hI j7 I y dif  I Il vI 1 I  I  VI LJ ya vi va I WV a4 I   3 LJ 0 Iw I 4  dvI I LTJ LJ fly vi a ILLM 121 I vf b iI I i TI I fPq u  I hA 4 Liij r yy U  LL 1q7  1L  Iih1 p7I I if w2 LKJ U  ed LA I 5 17 I wcz 7 iw F Ig Sj  VA Ii1 ftmi LL 7U  iI ddIMJ Ik1 wr viA Ja U E77e T4m  W7T tA 74 i4 i j1  01 Ik1 iFI t hrJ Ii L B i wI LJ aj IviJ I J F a 4 vFj  a a 1 bLi h1 Pe U 01 a1 U  LA VI rhL qmu vi U  FIIii A L4 LA Ar2AP IIKi I 4 I1 LKi WI hr TA LA rj IrA AJ in  wu itL hid jw EZIEJkh rm  uliL 1 Ili 1 If LA im y jj55Eh Y1 d I VI IA I a I1 7 I A LAd j1p4 IL Id iJ EI F ij i q 77 I F WI gtV pa LW I I IJ JII ri I aU    2 r qy iju LA 4MI A gME  0J A  qr AW jgiIj    A  jw p adi  U U p I A  mE g A saS 4il  zIIH4s I I Il 1  U t1 wgfl1f P1 I Ed1 V  I  Fr I I sdillUENL a 1V ht IiII1 EA M r u rIiLq  Wi  iidiMNU  WI WA a h4k VIP h72 b  dA I A m m  ii A p wr Ii wp ip hW ppx F I id di LkJ F Fpv 1mLhh vW FP r A pr EbJ pp 17 mm 1J 7 pp F b hdd p VP pp  wU IImIr kka ih TI fdl  iidi  pi AYi ijill Y ffffflhIU w ir qeiL j UVWt1 LI d1 fJj1Ti 7 rfIJtlI I I I q  lijiIIIIUEhb w WffUTU12i U LahdLkfiik F  ilIfff I iri iW kjiiIW wmt m T A I hlai U ffiii5i0JEML 7p tmJ F7 7 bm Fir r  AVU tiii A I1I A  ruY II EJ 7w I A w Wfff if  h iTiIjIN A iiiq yr ff7171 II Au 1i iiuidIdWaNP F aw  A4MiiIS aft NS aNNAS IhMaiFN5 WI 2hdII mmI  I rr LUd 1 I v1 pp 77777i1cftr F I Lid Li wI I Is vIw I r  7Ti I ai I hi wmj ed LLJ I I I Th7P 7 1 eqJ 1 5r hvJ Ill Ld ID t1v I hLVJ hV1 fgWI hIAJ F LJ hLU LVJ IIJ hvJ LWJ h1v4J hVJ IEVJ W77W1 Uf Id I hm1 hvJ vi mA A1dLLiL9IfV I iAhIIIIIiluIA  I iiik L1pq hhIIIILU4jSL  zJW  JIjdiiii mIIIix EMiihJ1UNNA Ih2h m A U Ltd La ua w  baa jJ pp mJ PIpp mIm4 Em 7J bJ hmImh A 1 4 Ki Ip p ppp 4 Pr 4 4 4 piiv pp 14i pp5 LA v Ew I  DL 1w I A71 di4 JAii j7  JEd I I A 1Ji I  jgj I  I k1dIIdi1M1A I  dIIiriNIA A iilLUiX I I J1111jjggw I  A5giiIJIJiI5 I  I  I   jIIIIN5E s IjjAd r  k iiiII 77I I 7 g diMiiw VP  Ia7a Frw La2 gi n pr I 34 I I 1 ali Iw4  I ali I I I I v AJAd II 1 ph mm we4 rww rj F 4i9 IA 51 iff 1k1 1A U 1  II 4Jm hirffi ifik 1LULl J 1151 b4r EU WI I ieg  4 wlJp TrII 6 A l4ji 1 a fl 7 EWIh1 i dill IJL NIl U   A Ir LIII j 1141  I 1ffff r  F 7jytiP111 f17hgqI iflr I eIi iN LJiI 1 It 4  iir a L Ib llllrnJ i1INII flfN JIJujr e4 IL 1Iuk iueiq I I 441 Ipu 2Jhi LllU rqpt gg r411 1   et1 ii lAb Wi jI yf EWZ AL L 4 994 cm ziI h x kh Fm ElliS p7 JuI laL 1I j   I 9I iiE iJhI1L 1iI0rd 14UI itu fl LIMIiIh1I IqmEq MII gh J A  ar f py  bLil prr aihAW iw 1geu  vI L     UL FLU I 1 Et ht Pib   bWXl b U LI LILJ a wv 4 e r pp uwl SI dhA hM b nt I  1tt  I3 Wd 7p r 4 V Ul bAP yd IJ p rjq y I p V Jr 1 IF I  kW ulI 8M A4WJw  1WL U bdm 1  4b pv 2 w  AAYW vv Lr Fr 0 V W I II4 su ri U hi F IA L WI VJbIL All hLi Iwb  ALAiEm V A Wi   d WL  r 4 41 WI WY p WV EY  v hkA ILiUu Nph  4 A buLJ aU A   qm 3 9 h FY ET7 w U Ti Wi r  V I Ii piJ Ad h7 di Lqq pprjJ L  Lmm Ip j wr 7 pp7 p  I     U qj I J ii MJJ jfrqjI z1Jyt a  vJ I 2h 1i1 I  F j71 qL A U J I tI du wI F  w p Ju 1W YE 4 IIMM ZIILL2 j idi Ijj L l qI11JfJ Fri II4MIDA rfqqffpf  LL 2  I  fj Pd7 pr pIa eli I I v41 k q LqYr Lqvr pi IF 4 i zuIJu 44j mu I I l I iI SIIEIIhX  L  p I N J 1A I  1t L 1 I eDit uI 4 Jiq JE 14 4 I M htapb1 pj jul 44 ii I PT V q f I f  404 4 e Ihi At pp uvla p  I  h1 L W I a iplu h71 h7 9Th vw Id Pfl L11l JIIU r dhII IiIliibi JIS ii111dIIi IiDI UItIJU I  Fww1 I 11Ifl Ii11w mi I dEIiIih I  IaI 4h j4 4w1 LtIh I U U r iWI aI F  qhI mmm vi vf k I w7i w7 i 4 U c  qqup eli el Iq al tww wIp I VI EI  q I 0 I I iqahi dh7 I a 4 a4 a4 iv iIf  a 3 31 VI a  w  a d I  FFIp  11 vI I 2 U4 I  Si I  Il 33 12 p1 SE p p VI fm   dI  I 7 w 2 jU I f  dI  ww 94 IUp w1 q FfL a1  a 7 I I hb hb   aI bW  a If Rqbj   m WT  0 ifl4 FLLIUA2 44 S4 a A   3 V I 7i7  dir aIi WI Iv I Pt I I  EE J iI P7v a I aI a4 q El 3 EIE yJ Th I 3V 7u9  4 4   uqaw  aI uq1  VI WV 9 3 EHDEL N ir IILU u  iv I An pw  a I a4 II I S d jI f h I pJ I p7J inab I d   0 d 5 0A A 7 iu LJ I vIUq pwa Id mu   2 3 I a4 U ddl I E Fr  5m I id  l inui  Id  a l I I 5  II I A  I U 3 vi IIv aIi u  Fr I IF j vi I I db I 7 7 w wYr fir 3 wIw vYr 2 a a I   7i V4 LI el r a a1 I  kIUMUi 2    4   I ULI J SI h I Aia VII i1 I 1 IiLi II JLIi L2IAL iu  Ihid  pa U  rbhi r  m   ziiIIiJ IE 1  wE  I vf a  1 fi J1  I U  U  r all I dI dI  dI zf II 3 yq U Na I IWI IT ii I q Vf  U dl UL I wziWU dI I P1 ui4z1 If  Ii I I  U Wj W0 cq uu Id 5 7 I VI p  L  tz di  al LU Y Lj U  L hi F i 4UL  Y w  U  I LA LKi LA mir U I h  U  Ii aI L1 upI1 dI  m1J i  I 6 J Lu   m4 kg   vi FI11 V WtU  U  i1 VI Iq I F   ill wTh bm LA x5 5 a p LY LLi jI a VI 5k 7 I ma Iaid jI  4 I 4 IWL D 7T  II 7 r nRd hiu1 hlIv Il i bL1 p icr z7J 1uiUII I  lila I 4 I4 K 4 tt IbW I I K 1il I   Ii II 9W II  ft 11  41  J 1Y ww   EL IqEE hI1QI1 4MOhi </field>
</doc>
</add>
