<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">5806</field>
<field name="name">HVC472659</field>
<field name="asr">noise and_you know it's beating them to die britain's prime minister called brown who was that stone them in that war hospital noise do_you cut the ceremonial plastic a distant aboard the sixteenth and of a sweep of the n. i. h. s. noise the national health service noise it was created noise but that's what breath the paper administration and nineteen forty eight noise to all of a forty noise at the port interviews noise health care two global population noise breath and whether it's not the minute updates problems noise mhm breath huge cost of running this is a racist and providing health care for everybody was breath noise grossly underestimated and all set noise sustained to pick up noise over the seven seas is grossly underestimated noise breath and it wasn't long before that's for sure projects began to be introduced for things like spectacles noise and for prescriptions noise noise the pros it instability freidy breath at the point of view c. piece of paper free health service noise not much noise the insurance based system that guarantees about united states the national health service is attacked by the system sorry noise texas noise oh sure yeah the countries we_have noise these con artists so that it is to cover the costs noise what do you think of noise tax base health care systems is it the way to them or noise should we use so this is like noise but it's in the united states which are based on it sure what's noise noise </field>
<field name="ocr">bti VT 1P7 LII b ml F1 Iii p1 LI AJ r1 e IIVi4 Fs1 IA 4i vF1  I Aid ppr rpp a 0 a S 4zi ri IaI 4 LZ  UIL L F ILL Ij WAm i 4E 7 4 L taa bLZ IWiP LJ LiJ lb I I hi  I  V b V L h4A LtL ww FL VII  B  LJ I  w I V Pu hL I w V md ru I IL LEJ me   iI w jvp JL BAli c Ae IM  wvF LA a di w Iw uJ FI A m FI U q  E L ib1 ib1 il 1 4 bd Pr I  mm IIRb LI ht iii 1I  pppp LJ Fr Nsa  xJ p1 Ph dJ mUlL LI ml dJ F dd Lg LIJ di dsi pU LJ evil fl F I  1 w  a  4 aiw  br1 LIE IM F wflrqp7 i Li i 116111  t  1 4a rvi V  m  44 I I  4 A 111 Na   hL q Yr I   1  4hdia b  LnI  t ppw F  q 4 4 ii 1J UHF1  pNi I q1J 4dIE LJ WI I riIi  Iia U U I w mb S 4 4 Kw cw idsIii iJ 1 JJ q  LIIi r4r1 mA 1L I  PIP 4   iiiJ Ai Iiiiw rv 52 uJ F vI ppI iiIh 1 LL  jE YI ii FI I urn Ff1 F ppr d L7 F1 q  </field>
</doc>
</add>
