<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">5904</field>
<field name="name">HVC492408</field>
<field name="asr">there is a junior music filler music so i mean one one thing about your project right now that she can be slowed down a bit like wind and i can't quite see where he's actually going_to hold it a bit of the camera noise so you_have two kinds of american spirit here back out noise okay part b. is from noise filler mentioned breath noise are these identified with they made port friend or did you initiate these afraid that i would point out noise o. k. noise that same game now noise i can't change here noise i think that society we have we feel i don't want to carry the lottery is buchanan right along a_lot_of weight and you've got to be said noise o. k. noise yeah music noise o. k. noise i mean each used to house on fire noise what's your friend are you reading noise yeah my war music staying here noise noise noise yes ma'am noise music my brothers music let me ask you music noise and what this witness noise you were wearing out noise that is that noise that please noise no not really music noise go to the government and that's this treatment noise filler noise i mean one of the things that interests me about the project that you're doing right now noise is it not noise that basically noise it sounds like you're experiments and would you like noise and i think that that's what artists do_you think that's what interests me about hard news noise not that it's all noise sounds good noise </field>
<field name="ocr">lAfAi wzuE dJJ 12 ijr IJI ItJ IlL WV Eu AM CAM XAJ EEtAW I d1 I  wj 1 Jill 1 L khES hW Li AMER L pIP mI 44 FhL 5 AN JJ L8IAN AM ERIc AMERI RI ij AMER IA AM E R I Cii IAK AM Eli  IAN AMER Al BAN AMEnicj IAN RIAM AM ERIi AMERIAI IAN AMERIAI AMER PIAN AM E R  Al AMER IBM E R I A N AMERIC Ja E P I A N RIAI ERI  A N ANI RIAI M ER I A N R IA N ANERIiI vJ R I A P AMER IDa AMER ER I A ERICAI mi DIME AMER I Al K I RI A N AMF RIjj RMERI A I ANE RIA RiAN AMER A AMERI R E A I A N IIAN AME Rical ER IA N AMERI AMER I Wa E A I C A N IAN AMER II I ER iAN AMI El I AN AMI LI IRIAN AMER II IlIAN AME a RIAN AME KaIJ AMER IER I AN AMER I Jj aERI AMER SERIAN AM B5tIA AM E R I Al aERI AMEAI IMERI RIAN AMEAI RIAN AMERI ERIAN AMER ERIAN AMER rnERIAN AMER S I iii A N AM E R I Al xI I ERUAN RIAN AM E a I Al AMER IC E RI AMER IC Al AM E R IC A1 ERIC AN AM E R I Al A N E R I Al ER   A N A I IJ iAN AMER I qj IAA ml A M I J AMERg AM  AM I A I ruIIg xa w4 Eli U  4 N RIa U III  A N AMER AMER I  U a ER I A N AMERIC AMER A N AA RI  AMER RI4 I IC A A N RI C A ME RI  Jj RI  A  E IC A N 4 N ii Ill C 4 lie  A AE II IC A N u5 6 dj I i A mI wirl ms DhMLl 4 AMLI II AMLI 111AN AMERI i ERICAN AMERI1 IAN AMEft ME  U XL 4N AM E U II Eli AMLRU NI DhMhL L ww EEIAN LRI ii  AN AMERI EI4N Db Nb I itd ri  N ANLRI AME xJ ADq AM 3UA Eu  4 N pr7 ANhII kJ jd a Ill AMI AMLUI 1 AMII dI AMLI C A N x1J AMLI LdhJmEiIIi ERIANI h AMLI rwpji AMLI U AMERI AM E AM L a IC 1 LI h M  NJ AMI AMLI y I ALI AMER II hi AMERI AMER II I lull AM LI LJ II BERI AMLI hE RI LJ 8hI U  CL I EL hi vi iw Iki iL L4 Ni F4 LL I j wsu  up L4r t 11 tAr ti v U i 1 i ti V ti V i4m 1 v vu F  Iv ti V K U El U  ti r Ur  U v U r  i  U U r ti   V IE V pp ti V 1 U a  I 1 v 4 3v p  B I IA v IILl tJ4v pP  5  I   I3r I 15 iilr 5 V  V  A w 4 hAt luAu 1 LI U   Ix Ew1 Ip Xl WfT ru Av 3 I U fi f9 U I FWa I  WE PF fr </field>
</doc>
</add>
