<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">7169</field>
<field name="name">HVC767499</field>
<field name="asr">noise i this is chasm that she knew in probably to talking about to call all these different on new tropics substances thank you noise smart drugs noise you can actually used to stripped cotton machine and make yourself smarter noise no i learned about these various substances initially by reading a book called smart drugs new trains this is a book called smart cards to the next generation noise and then another book called brain boosters breath i think there's another group called brain candy or something and then breath anywhere in a whole bunch of stuff on your head about it and read a bunch of medical studies double blind placebo controlled crossover studies and breath studies done in europe anyway and initially started perch hearings some of these new tropics breath a few years ago and experimenting on noise noise using nor sure isn't getting pink it's good breath and i noticed that some of these do illicit noticeable effects noise one of them and it's the career breath which was re classified by the f. d. a. is nutritional supplement i mean you can just buy it over the counter noise the united states although i was just recently re class five back to injure or by the f. d. a. so breath and the substance and we are here breath this is called shear is seen can spell p. i. r. a. c. p. t. a. m. noise no it's a number of with each class noise noise or filler breath filler grouping of smart drugs known as the breath i really don't do rumors breath he is filler is breath this is the filler the verse your journey tomorrow this is a map showing the filler breath and hence filler problem solving abilities creative thinking noise it's supposed_to work by filler noise increasing the breath the radar which information can flow from the right hemisphere that bring to the left hemisphere the brain breath well this largely live near drivers should be tried on breath how the court this close in which is like the boss breath in there the information superhighway connecting or to bring hats together noise the theory being that your right brain is associate with noise creative thinking abstract about it music louis freeh is where logical rational thinking breath oh yeah and that_he bring these two has ukraine closer together as opposed to noise yeah he sure i have a school is supposed to raise your right you as much as thirty points on the standard s. i. q. test breath it's also supposed to noise help you noise it by filler noise breath making more fish in the process by which you_are noise brain uses a subtle coleman breath i mean or transmitter sushi with memory that will clash on long term ridley breath that's what we're going to take breath sure as you can you're all set to take filler stuff called noise colon used to treat noise you know stink kohl invited her to be breath read to take less it then there's a new guinea pigs your solar products to the issue fish oil noise what was breath there is things break down and breath filler so called me breath still become we urge our uses pre person in your body heat noise noise if you don't see the so called leaders noise or some sort of cohn supplement breath then i'm sure she can mike i should bring the news up most of_this noise a cell calling you can do attitude that can and it noise breath this is true reverse effects were noise breath you know don't you down a few brain uses up all of this so called the stores you if you try breath cheers you_can can lately but there's another one that you can get a call and_i are seated breath there's also one call box or she can wear trail that breath and_i are she tends more powerful noise where you can get this other one car noise yes noise frohnmayer c. g. m. which really powerful noise you definitely get a use of cloning preacher wrestle calling three cursor supplement this smarter noise breath get what it is noise you know it's a lot stronger than that sure she can't sleep ten times stronger than doesn't taste very nasty noise i assume will suddenly be layered of before filler breath now a totally and gene filler breath it's actually a hormone you can breath when a driver for this stuff when your tongue breath when they're adversely you know mr. sleep a lot more effective it's a hormones released by that and_you will and bring breath this is so she was should pay and rhythms of results that biological clock it and tells the print or sleet and issue dreams a lot more intense breath filler and i think that we use that is noise the way john noise on the shoe sure to models tired like recognition or christian or short noise noise music noise yeah breath breath merger earned him a whole noise stand tall one otherwise known as thailand noise here the capture of what this stuff read all the precautions and their actions were not noise breath filler it's been taken balls anti seizure medication noise it's mostly workers this larger than just the last election where ten grand one owner owns the barn noise breath and since most of like filler breath to mary no ways in the break noise so you_can have a clear mind focus inward focused music recently have experiment around these other smart your call breath mona does feel or mode back at all breath noise which is filler and like a studio noise noise breath we'll be taking you can actually if_you continue to use and stay awake for several days at a time noise it increases your brains billings noise stay away noise are there and sleep deprivation and i know is that helps you filler concentrate it increases your attention span noise c. d.s sit down and study for long periods of time a particular subject breath unfortunately neither the study torn nor the more gentle breath can really be combined with the tears seen ten noise noise breath filler breath noise it's you want_to avoid doing that noise and they're kind of us are jerks that can be used by themselves noise noise breath no they are wrong breath there also noise if you want_to breath further enhance your intelligence your ability to learn and is suing new information he'd you know this season the blaze breath with experimenting with home health system noise yes noise which was the voice that has these clips include two year loops need put a filler a true john noise he uses trends continue select or interesting ration breath noise you cannot use its insuring your brain waves and elsewhere noise which is supposed_to be conducive to music i think if you use the office them breath noise in conjunction with this merger is noise you_can really learn stuff a_lot faster so anyway it's worth trying noise </field>
<field name="ocr">uI EI  L1 9 i Aum K  L1 11148 I F I Il L1 11 U1 EL Iw  LaF La 4  IC aihm ii L1 J7  I1  L1 I a h  VA mm r L1 mma L1 Ew 4 w  w  UWj L7 5j FM  UI LE1 L1 U A  mI L1 L1 L1 iLh  12 I1 L1 yr I   1I L1 L1 EUmuimmmm 1 I i L1 L1 L1 I  L1 L1 L1 L1 LI L1 L1 L1 U Aid L1 U  p U  11 L1 L1 Jmb 5 fimum L1 uI  a p  uI L1 Lv1 I Aab w 5El  LL Lwvl L1 U1 m  L1 U 4L UI F w  mm 1I Lev L1 b1 Lw a uI 1 EbiP I L1 LA U1 L1 wJ L1 bhJI L1 iVJ U1 uI IYm L1 II 9g rrr L1 991 L1 Yq 4mima L1 p  V U1 Mq L1 1 I  Irv  1jr I2 yYCR UI I UI UI U iwmE9t L1 L1 L1 uI  I la IEhEE I Cl j Ivwc a i U U L1 L1 L1 U m PP  I gg a L1 5 I g41j  vi L fqIIW   U  U hmtW wi L1 1 IAw VP bhL L1 p L1 L1 L1 uI L1 N L1 L1 L1 L1 UI L1 Ed7  Lv L1 II pu J  I mJ Ka I ui LI L1 L  Lv1 1api L1 L1 L1 L1 1  1I I  L1 I1LL ii  A h 1uv 11 L1 prj 1L P  1i L1 ui ui L1 FE L1 L1 II  L1 Iw Fmms L1 L1 L1 Jr L1 pqI U1 L1 L1 EA  uI L1 L1 EL hIL Uv L1 L1 w  U fly U L1 w  L1 UI L L1 L1 L1 L1 L1 L1 pppi I I 1I L1 UI bm IdI L1 Wi L1 uI U L1 L1 4 L1 rv2 L1 L1 U Ip1 ui L1 UI vi LL I Iw IL F Kvl rwJi iJI iI Ir JIm L1 L1 k  L1 3I Ld p pIpi 4  ml L1 mI L1 FU  uI up L1 L1 1i L1 L1 p 5 Lw UI U L1 Lav I Zriuui F mm 11 L1   L1 L1 yi r Ld1 L1 pIp  5 L4 UI L1 L1 Lpl L1 Lv1 UhIh  L1 L1 L1 L1 L1 U ml  uI L1 L1 PUhUIWk  Uvl WA a uImm U L1 L1 LaI 1w 11 m1 L1 w U  U mr w bh mmuUIma A ff ppp U L1 L1 I  L1 UI L1 L1 WAD U a  L1 L1 ui ml A I Fm L1 A  L1 iT 11  h pr 7L hiU p iJ L1 L1 wNsi Iw 1  u FEW I L1 L1 L1 Lvl Ld Lvl EILW  L1 L1 L1 L1 L1  N JJ b1 L1 II  II L1 L1 1I 1I r u Ely L1 a nr 1 r h PP4 I I L1 L1 ml   Sc  Ii Ii U 9AA I  UI LL L1 L1 I uI UI a U EhE5J V I w  id F Im1 L1 Fr W L1 U IIp  uI L1 I IJ L1 L1 L1 L1 91 A AL WIL L1 L0 I1 V A  L1 1I L1 L1 L1 riI L1 L1 L1 L1 L1 L1 Eq L1 L1 L1 U aT Eu I  1I  I L1 UI L1 zu V ag ALE ammm1 pa f7 r  I wai e1 mq 1I rEEF I nipi L1i rJ L1 lSm LLe Ir17 IF  L1 L1 L1 Im I A UI L1 UI A   q a Lav S vtmI J JI L1 L1 L4jJ F U k II JI rv 4 UI lw I UI ww   I  V4  ri v4 Iv I lIq UI r7A rT7xAI ri ww  h I Ia ww  I  I  wp qq L1 F Itb m UI 5vA  5 UI U r7 L1 L1 L1 L1   UI 9 L1 qq L1 B A  U  itp Lw  U L1 L L  F4 U a IpI L1 L1 L1 Fr2q L1 L1 L1 F ILl r1S TW1 El   L1 L1 ml I d v1iqE ad IA APU mfl m  L1 1 1w 1 AImi L1 L1 i El m  L1 L1 ri if pp L1 L1 ir7 L1 L1 L1 E1 L1 v  E1 mI L1 4 L1 1 I9 EkEd yI mi L1 r tA ff L1 I  L1 L1 L1 L1 L1 UI IF j L1 L1 I  11 h 9 lA L1 1I L1 uI iii a j1 I UI uI Lv1  U ml  i  1A F Iv  A L1 L1 L1  we A 1uI my I L1 1A 1I I1 Ib W 1  U 1dmLguEhIh  A   I 4j EL  F1Jb Lia II L1 p  L1 ii L1 Em tin Lv1 ui Si L1 ii a  h  R5 AU FI7Y L1 I L1 La L1 L1 DATh1 UI p1 p5qu UI   u1 I  MLI L1 L1 p wm UI A  L1 p U L1   I L1 S I k  pII m UI UI icu L1 I wkIju wTqW L1 L1 L1 vA L1  1 Er A L1 L1 1 FJ I L1 L1 L1 5 L1 PEW Lv WY EP P Fr ii  1 U Li 1 I L1 L7 1 Vp  i  Jid pI b  veI ww iLTA w r  L1 1  rnII UI ru h v1 UI Lv1 m a mu La UI L1 L1 L1 j4 uI 1I I V A  L1 ma w7 r  A1 uI I N 7A  rA  L1 L1 Ll I J  I hq F   U Lwl L1 L1 U1 7q L1 ir u I U L1 UI Pr wt  r  L1 L1 mmJ1 qq L L1 jAbWdF I 1 L1 L1 L1 VP L1 Pmrn a m U m j 1 pIp pIp Lvi 11 p  uI w  uI U wN Fad 7ii p Iiiu p U WL  Lw1 uI I  uI 21 uI uI 1 F U II f A ITI 4 iar IpI L1 A Ai  I V4 t  5  v4A  U L1 L1 Lv w L1 bI I  U1 lima 1I LEVI L1 U1 p   p U L1 L1 Jr V L1 I 11 L1 uI L1 uI L1 UI L1 L1 L1 VP Tw a i4 L1 WV bU L1 L1 F iiq F ILk L1 FJ vpu bmJ LuI L1 w4w I uI uI uI 11  mE Lv L1 4q 11 a VAL I s  U L1 U a ib I 1 I F rni UI h I L1 LA WI L1 aI if1  L  L1 L1 1i I  Lyl L1 b7U L1 uI v   Li L1 L1 VAr  L1 g  VA   UI L1 L1  U L1  a L1 L4 L1 ffi uI U rm L1 L1 V  A UI U  V A S L1 pu L1 I ir E3L12  w L UI uI L1 L1 VA m I L1  U A L1 iY1w j U PIp 4 w mm Fwi kI L1 rEA uI uI IE LA1 7r pp uI W2 U wqw Lv1 F p A 7Vi  U1 w  r A L1 iP A   U  wU rL L1 1I uI FYA ui wr wEq I L1 uI L1 jlh L1 11 rAm M L1 fhl L1 U II r mm i w  L1 1dJIr LdI L  L1 iI L4rw pp p F diii Ivj  L1 iI FyI L1 I Fq I  U  I II L1 zi wI VA L1 Tu Lhm U bEhm A Ly1 gb WLI L1 uI L1 L1 L1 L1 L1  U  L1 uI L1 p L1 L1 IPhuEa 7 r NA  frw L1 EEIL U L1 L1 4I L1 U k  L1 L1 L1 L1 5  U L1 L1 7IT  L1 L1 EmE I L1  A  L1 UI rEly  Lv1 Lvl rj L1 p  L1 Le ibm rIA 7II jh  uq mmm L1 ME L1 1I I i A Lv L1 U Linv A  L1 iiIIEhIL Ai LEVI W A L L1 L1 L1 Iwi L1 uI L1 L1 Lvl I  iI  U  94iI Lv1 L1 Lv1 IN L1 I L1 w  AYI 4u U Va L1 Lv L1 L1 L1 I L1  4 uI  m L1 U Li Eqv Lv1 L1 L1 rnu L1 U Ntm L1 V uI I fr L1 UI U  S w  P a pp FW L1 I L uu9FIW L1 ru L1 L1 w  L1 L1 iJ L1 Lv S  L1 L1 IW w wrwwu L1 S qq S 7Iq L1 Levi E7W LL 1L L1 Ei 4 a 4 4 4 il 4 4 4 4 L1 UI w    a L1 1 7 U L1 L1 L1 uI L1  S V  A  L1  v    L1 uI L1 L1 L1 uL  L1 L1 uI P A Uz L1 UI U1 w A I1 uI V A  FrW 7i ri L1 L1  diI L1 pm wq 1I L1 rTdI U L1 1 uI L1 uI UI iI U uI Li L1 L1 WI Uvl r  L1 UI uI L1 L1 FuJ L1 Jz7 mmg L1 UI L1 r jq L1 L1 Iw L1 1I IlL 11  L1 4g uj L1 uI UI UI Le L1 I El  L1 L1 Lv1 L1 WF 11 ID urk   L1 L1 L1 W9 L1  11 L  m1 A  L1 UI uI Tii L1 h  uI LibEb  1I a LA U Er a mu4 E L1 uI LwI L1 L1 L1 L1 L1 L1 IdI U L1 L1 F I  wa L1 WD 1i rr L1 I w L1 L1 Uv1 4 uI UI w  j L1 U  7Ii  Ld1 L1 L1 U  U L1 U U  AJ pep ui  V  ui L1 L1  w r4 EvA  3 L1 U uI L1 L1 Lw L1 Lii  4jWhr L1  w w  Ll 1 w  L1 U dL1 L1 A Up L1 uI L1 L1 w  L1 L1 L1 L1 LE Lv1 L1 ui uI L1 m  L1 LLU lIh Li uI Li U1 LI uI uI KTLF 4U L1 uI L1 ri wu JVA I  49  p  L1 cq L1 JPL  qp I  L1   w L1 Email UI hA kI 1 Ii  b4AL I2 WaML  U mL WlrA Lv1 Lv1 1 L1 L1 u1 irnI uI r 1 Eki 11 ha L1 L1 my L1 L1  I L1 L1 ppv k I L1 Esgw 1 uI vi ILI L1 4w L1 A VUU Iwp  A L1 I  VI aUq U L1 L I b L1 I  I I  J w1 L1 71  1I KIU L1 ms ii U L1 q9 VI ui L mm L1 I  iinh I I  I  11 rjU 4  L1 L1 jJ p  hh LmmZd1 L1 L1 L1 L1 L1 ELi Li PIE W 2 p  JI 1 Lv1 pm ILJIEJ F U L1 VA  L1 L1 V LW L1 L1 U L1 Lv1 U aI w  L Y ui L1 5 UVI L1 1I 7k    L I L1 Li L1 L1 L1 U U 1 U1 wI I L1 1JU UI Uvl urn U FP L1  p L1 L4 IiIq irn L1 1i wiIwU  U Le AIh  L1 Li  Ii 12 mi w qw L1 Ef L1 UI Lv1 L1 1 L1 L1 U I  L1 Ad upE 2 1 I  L1 4 L1 e lrrI Jw A  7 4 V L  0A vwI  j  i Ahd rI p L1 CIIUEIL jF5 uI EL 2 yr Ii L1 L1 UI I  U Uh AhE uI 1 Uvl Lv1 L1 iII Uvl  Lv1 1 L1 rni i  I s a rni  VA Eff L91 L1 L1 U F L1 Lv1 Lv Uv Lv tin P1 Lv v1 IL q UI rh nm mq9 I Tu W z7 L1 L1  I LiI uI tiITui LI Ii I  11 mmu 13 mAin a 2 L1 IFI El   dJ L1 L1 L1 mmuiIEhIEh   1 L1 L1 L1 UI a L1 L1 L1 L1 Li 5 L1 Lv mmIIzmmmm Er Ii  ill Jm w  rq L1  U I1 L1 ua L1  4 p iii 1w wi4 uI iium7 5t2 fAU w  L1 L1 11A  A dL 2 b p IIb1 L1 75 L1 L1 1 11 A Lvl mJ L1 L1 L1 L1 hmmhhheLh  L1 rU uI 15 UL U ei Lid mmq L1 if i uI U Uv1  q K LaZ L1 U L1 j L1 11  Urn L1 L1 jJ 4P ui L1 v7qin mu L1 1I 1I uI L1 L1 L1 IL ii S  Fm L1 L1 TI  1 </field>
</doc>
</add>
