<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">7825</field>
<field name="name">HVC026344</field>
<field name="asr">i was right noise music noise noise go ahead and breath you know what i undertook a zoo to you noise i mean where are the day to you noise that we noise are are breath the noise the noise noise i heard breath the noise you know noise there_are filler noise noise you_know the the word noise yeah noise music breath yeah it sounded noise noise noise i mean what are you know either noise noise that implies i noise music it's all right right noise all_right thank you so here right noise what i mean noise it noise not all that rhetoric breath that was a hill noise one second noise breath noise noise yeah yeah yeah sure i really want and you think ranches or may not seem to me noise noise yeah noise music that will object noise breath well noise yeah noise let me noise you can see most era noise a lot of donovan long gone and she's just feel like well off breath although no but noise fundamental noise sure where to get in that area that i noise yeah noise noise well noise it noise yeah noise music i know a noise very similar in you noise or it's the only i can ha noise noise music noise we have for prisons noise noise noise filler filler any of you noise noise i don't know what that have been that_he saw since saturday breath had he aimed through a lot of breath what you think you letting me go ahead noise a half dozen more he gets a lot of courage to exit here you know noise all right noise sure noise noise noise noise breath we've got to noise noise noise noise you know noise what noise noise talk to noise i think there is blood noise noise yeah breath noise well you know don't always tell me noise my i want you would clearly show the blood d._n._a. and i have breath music noise i mean he's there noise noise noise well the thing noise music we'll show you that noise all right and this is how do we have come here this week a runoff breath music noise breath well noise yeah noise right noise noise c. n. n. and i'll carry no no noise i have to to take even clean music so i don't see noise noise music noise he really said music noise music noise see john yes you_are young sets policy music and what are the is that whatever it is really sweet mouthpiece noise well i don't buy fish eaters breath noise is that right now from our own right music noise noise great noise be great noise breath music yeah music noise music all_right music noise music yeah yeah noise music what i mean this thing music what do you think well that was their right noise noise well noise yeah music well this is where the issue not only have about not about me noise me i mean we've ever had that are are breath noise and and this year breath what she said it's a good money when you want to take a seat and_he noise noise there probably will be to see what he can noise watch would surely lilies there is reason enough to fit it was wrong noise right it's a very few of the full force of breath filler it's it's gone noise noise she had not with him and not all right now breath no more noise than than than filler filler yeah noise noise o. k. what about a film is to back me noise and if they don't know noise you noise not noise yet breath filler and so what noise tom noise that they want noise noise sure breath noise the other noise music i'm sorry noise it does i'm sorry noise all o. k. well i think the house does yes noise noise she's my little beings breath and it's not we're not surprised noise and noise why music noise noise i think that maybe they didn't do it right noise yeah noise noise noise yeah noise right noise he's written a downer noise yeah filler this noise noise yes noise filler like i remember noise okay well why don't all will noise yeah noise noise it's brown noise great grandma noise well i agree noise from what i remember the profit that it wasn't worth on the t. v. noise record but your your your house breath filler filler it seems to talk back noise noise noise noise noise o. k. right noise breath well the numbers are there and i don't fit and they will mr. altman head anthony i think you can consider front arm she should breath i promise noise why didn't he noise he noise of it our h. and noise breath yeah it is not an face friend paul starr noise in temporary comes from noise when you noise that noise the timing breath i don't think sound alike noise yeah noise noise noise i think that since monday and the ox noise i am noise but noise in atlanta noise with nothing and without any of us noise you know and all of you who the killer noise irv chapman c. marginalize me who's here right here music what should breath filler noise lied or not breath filler the noise breath well noise yeah breath noise they're swell noise and you will never be indifferent thanking placed on top of me trying out a theory is is that that's so breath how we pay breath this is not noise could i have no need noise okay noise when i was noise what filler we noise are noise in the right noise let me get noise breath yeah filler filler a man noise sure yeah i'm not involved noise yeah noise yeah it's a very tricky noise didn't fit yelling noise you_don't need to return to that whole thing noise what happens if you know you know it happens it and i don't know noise and the short answer and have another third planet music noise noise okay noise music yeah yeah yeah </field>
<field name="ocr">aL w v1 IL1I  F mm J1 LWL J7 ml 4 I I F 4t TW IdL I 1 44xt  I1 4 w 1b Fr  1 q5 Ipz stm dhh93I4hw F TI I L4J  b AU IIdI hb I Eb mhJ j4 q I  pI pr LPz S AeqaE VEWK eAwL4 L f LWi UOb pri p  Pu U  Ii Iwi LNa  I pvIJJ AL ijm in LkI QI r V K Ffl Jhj F  PJ I dRj r  gq LJLC DL11 mm  w E 4 EAJ E1 LI r1 Wj Elba fMi el 7  e 5e Imi Pr F pPr JhJ J ft pw rpm Ld II La I II LI lET Lii Ib El  Ed 91 9 Li 4i LE a It 1 IE IEJ F7 FqL I I  I U II i u1 mu A Rh CJU Ld 5I  w 4 II Ilmi hZq LUYFZII1 I gI I  Vi I V q FF2 LPA wa LI F tLK  I X L  FY mk I Um 4 A pj  K 4q4 wpq hdL1 wj ppr dJ  puI kIhA mt i 8  V hEh 1A S Fr si j bII 1 p wu iA I JPd L V  II 4p L1S  rp1 I k hm hU L I 9Am U bIr I 7a  L1 1 I tAS it p VI IY Iu i JI iI EY qq LWI WbhLIWI 13VZI jui tILI 4 EYu Epw F i4r PI Il U Tm 1 UVI E F fri 1L  V J IWbhfr d hih 5A IuIiJ Eli p F ff Nfl Dfl Fi IItp 7 EY  1 FlA hhl Sri I 1WAIJJ Pr LL zu iI cTU ppir II g  6 Pu  I  If vw p rp ULI  p IL LJ Jj inIAMJ JJ I  vat rp 2J Ih LJ 4 bL I ft rjS IN td F k I LJ HI TXM rpEIp Ii iEu w SS LJ W pup wr 7Y I  LT tYI InI a  F JAJ pmmA w I7 iI Ji pJ JJm pfl 4Mbi mm r1 EZW rt r1 mmA rI rI r  ErI FKd rI K1 c1 9771 wr i I Is ILII II 1a2  JJ rI J1 LL LL Fi iS27 I  Eu  urT w  IT JAI hft Tili ri 45J4 Tr Jj AL JJ a U U mJ LJJ bb 54 hsW Fri 1 121 Ja II 4r Eu  LJ LEL LJ Jj LN N mJJ mLL Jj F JaJ LL La LLL yj tI WI I y dmj bJ   LJ rpm mJ mJ fl g1 vI LII Wy rI I 711 rI rI F rI LL mIJ r1 LJ iaIm rU LI LLLI I iE I IPIwt LL 5 aI rr E  K V K V mJJ If As JJ LJ il Pdh VP IVPV1 pd dPW1 U 4J avPvh vJ 4j ut p A PwIg 1 PwI qmi p  pi 1 d iILJ1 It imJ5j Ft K Ft II L F lIZ I  I 6 ImJ il iw U dP4 pq Ii p 4 p  1Ii dP JfId  EL1 vi Wi kL2J U 4 rfI L4h1  EAJ wu  1i 2J wu mu lip U pm hhq i 5 PI A1 U iILS1i 1I J 11 WI 1II WI 4yr w WEV lip U d LWW   Pg LV rPi4 jYgjj4 IiwP LJ I ft w  WI Fill fft lIe 1II 1d wRNA 0  Id 4 Ne PS trPft r pq ruwq V r  I d I 9 Iid Iw 1dd IJj tVw4 19 NJ fr p Nd I j IvLNd I j I  a m rLN bIJ bf II U YIW IaP11i4 dv1 wru a 1II LiIJ IJ AJ m1 m1 mjg F Id IN Iw 1d Id Id L rAil 1 ma rI Id III q B I   I rwH U I VNJ VN VfvH 15 TFfWI 1vH B7  T ill VN a mA VfVH IF U mA p74 Ada 7 ull U T me pm LA6IrI IJq LN ii 9 SI I SI P tuJ II L  bz 14W v1 I be Ah1 If Fi mt JL yu P4 PIYI5 APJ tfu lIFE me S eEl Id Lii aji mmYpw LU wr rr rw h Ed Lff Fr Uk  Ua jim ERA ff rL qjJ fi fi mi vu IL I 11 A III LI LJ L1 e  4 L4L wvu W1 7W1  V2YU sri v1 Yrk in  W4J Li1 V L1 LI uIEI SI L1 ik L i 4 Itv CAJ tr tbUuI 4 Nu   U  a b 4 U hi ri Iv gwi tl if mjT 4d VI II Irh r pmv 6un Itv1 ui hLi Pd Li I EL bL LfL a LL 4S K V U S  bAL 11 v4h 97W1 1I 7v Fr tidi fl tifl 5 LI Uja A2 ih diIn WJWU SI LI diifl ImgD Id I n ur  WA A tdsiI LimP Am wmEIE wb i4ri di V VfP U U diA1 wi gyuu 4 n uyU1I UPVu II wja tiuiI IpJ dVIOIiI bmh 4 vvV I4 AV1 J V U jv LJ U  U  LA il  5 pjb piqi L5AJ I4 Uh1 mwm LP IL LL1 4I r  1 111 LL IUiJ LI1 ta vF Lf eEl miri p 1t uI bL pI WI mw I  qw ha LLJ L  1 L  4 mm LI Li  r 0 E a ILAI bIN K A 4Q fI K LJ K i7 w Li wL4 471 I  Pu a L  U LW L2L B I Pp I Li i11 IA1  pg FK wu LJ LIII J V qY I4 I I 1 I  hU5 I ELL I ih1 WbEbl LAI rj F VV LPJ VdV U a Pr EKLi qqE PL F 1 v rw FU vjb 1wY LwnmgHOfYW tioriwig Kom Home Learning m 21 I Laan16fl9 Name Nafiw Home I Home Learning Learning Mania ILL Learning Home Lamklg Home learning Home Hom FU sq NowO Nom YYw JII uJ Lrp rW I 1fl r I rni Aa Ys i 4wqw wi pp b U a bIT hd A U U4 4 I 91 IJ 7 mShl TW h w p A mimi Uu IILL lip Ar AJL JJ su IA mm  V  D vuI Ni </field>
</doc>
</add>
