<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">7946</field>
<field name="name">HVC065058</field>
<field name="asr">making half blind dove tails using the the wall d. w. six eighteen d. handle rounder breath and_the porter cable forty to ten dovetail jake the half blind dove tail as a strong mechanical joint breath that is pasta visually interesting breath it is the preferred join for drawer construction noise start by securing the fees inside of the drawer in the game noise then the temple is lined up noise the guy bush ian and dovetail bait that are included with the g. a. current stall noise using the factories that that stop on the j. the dovetail bit is set to the proper exposure to route the joint noise set the round of base flat on the edge of the jake's template to the right of the work piece noise turned around or on breath and move the route or across the face of the work until you reach noise finger of the template breath bits like pointing to noise reduces breath littering the killing breath one due to the first catholic finger in to the guy but he bottomed out breath rolled around or around to the next thing here to the right continued in that manner and plead noise you be proud of the work noise i'd noise thank noise okay noise breath noise noise on clamp on work pieces and assemble the joint noise yeah noise looks like a great day noise </field>
<field name="ocr">FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN h FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN FIN I4 C  i 7 Lz WA xtz p IpL ID 10 I 1 F p  5 3 1 up 5u Pr  I  I  I rimIj EI JA Wi pPrj Ez W A I UK lurk wag p7J jJ Id 9 I  I T LJ LL hmi m1 m15 ie Ui El aJ r 1 El U LJ  ax zf IF Ef IE iii uw  Pr 9W r9 I I9 IhI uIuEII RhuirnP burI9 Pr Pr jJ IE rr I1 P7 w ii w ii 7i w ii iii jUL IE 4 IE 4 6lit m  IE r1 IE IE Kiv I I Vd1 2j I V WU JY JY JY FL JY JY 1k rT iern PT Li A nfl U r7u IL I V  SW 7 U 5 U I F IE I IF IE WI IE IF IE IWI Af T7t L2 Pr Id Li rrJ 9kW Ew p U ml LE LE I r 7 I rr IE I IE JJ pI hL2 JJ Jj If IE r4Z 7 U I  EJL LL W1 I I JY aLLL2 rz U Pjgu rJ 1mb P rLJ mmE jEZWE kJ L ia I j7 I U pp I F rr n2I eEr hal bi I  rL JJ IE 1 U mID1 HI El I I ru IEyE1 Ij IE Em I 1  U I I  WI 0 IE IE IE IE mIq mIq mIq mIq I Iw iii 7 LI I hij 5ia v5 4 II </field>
</doc>
</add>
