<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">8626</field>
<field name="name">HVC334586</field>
<field name="asr">they can with the s. and so does the_other day i can we're going to call him day betsy ross is dead that he had not lands think enough o. k. now when we do that to you right bryant saw dustin yeah he noise have a right already found this noise yeah okay we're going to shoot rounds are asking yeah right noise o. k. noise all_right noise now where we just laugh so i'm sure you understand that noise and more noise so we're going to put this in your city is pressed on foot noise breath yes is stress isn't done around here so we'll move this up a_new low in any way grievances noise the irony of it noise filler ted as you know long grass noise o. k. noise don't turn it on music noise well that is you know breath and right yeah noise yet there is a major flap of saying you know right up the race breath noise what the lesion out noise well what do you not noise it's all yeah you're kinda nice sounds as though aren't there times okay and then noise the noise top of that and the machine is going_to_have the reverse noise yeah i can say that noise yeah noise noise well it may be next gee this is in her eye noise her five kittens noise no well yes they are scenes that you write for that noise noise noise noise noise not breath and these are then noise the its yeah maybe seen bad numbers noise o. k. noise looking down on given gene acts with that that they do next noise that sent the end of that that i had_a really nice and pleased that a_little houses orion aren't there noise as i can get a missile noise yeah </field>
<field name="ocr">WrA U   F1 Fi II U Li I VP9 Ir ir4 hi K  pf am r ii aJ  1 1 V  E A I hdi1  I mkP T mLP F 1 WV r pp vu WV Ipj 5fI vu vI wu 1r EJI Mi Ai 1 WY ppp2 7 a P U FYI Ki PEW EI Yu V Lr LPJ IrJ Li mi aLJ BJ2 Tn Jj LF Nj h I h I WY Ep yin WV I IJ ppy ppyY L2 ifm   N vu vu vu qE Yu vI mpj U LA   P1 I N I ILr Nj   mqLP 1 r u ii  9 mJ Ic I I I Na a py    Iv 1 ar pEj PF pJ pJ U L LP2 LAJ Iv Ll   Wa A Ti I I 1 Ii p9j aP rr Mi L12 alp  J I Fv mr I  5A EA Ea inIL  X mmL  1 7 LJ jEJ 4 qb m4 rid jJ fr wF Tmhd vqY b4 YY Fvi V pr Fr k7i rT  jv  2 1 j7 YY ru p Ypi f YE V Ta EL  pr bhh VA V x1 lwVA V Ypp  A 9E7 UjI VIdI If fr Ta Ta IIw Yr JAd  I Fw du JR L1 I  P q UI PPaLiq AM pI F Frqj F4d F1 LF Eli 1P h wp6 wv I  Jj WI mJ L21 PIP uyP I  I  ri ma mmaPI P2 Li mr WWL F ri LV LV w1 </field>
</doc>
</add>
