<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">8751</field>
<field name="name">HVC383791</field>
<field name="asr">breath maybe it's going to noise the cooperative i'm sure and letting us think famine and clean hurt years today breath for the first thing you want_to do is sort of flipped the ear back like this to you_can get a look in five breath to push the hair away breath and you can check and he if there's a lot of dirt and lax or it looks pretty breath the ear lobe is actually quite clean breath and healthy looking o. checked the other one to breath to that noise if i could have it for you to get in with your cat checking breath periodically maybe a_couple_of times a week for any lacks the debris that might go about breath she's a little bit a lack spare some gonna show you how to clean the ears now breath what i do with a cat he'd here's our that's clean is probably just put a_little bit of money breath filler here are clean and i didn't hear cleaner on the cost breath and then just put that you're back noise and like the way breath noise on the outside in a little bit to blacks noise can you see breath and then noise mr. perot noise sasha cleaning one_of the things you_want_to remember to do breath it's always to lift out noise otherwise you have noise breath and_he laughed down into the ear canal and you definitely want don't want_to do noise breath so you start on this earth that breath and you why noise out and she'd go noise he there's a little bit of blacks there breath that we can noise breath more than that noise next step that you just use your little kids have been getting a cracks accredited in her ears breath we can't do this a little bit of lax on that q. ten noise even so he let her interests were noise clean breath can have a hundred noise our hearts until can have them actually hitting on right now and that's vertical canal breath and then that your count coast breath and breath before you hit the year term so you can't safely use a q. tip breath to clean out anywhere noise earnings there noise </field>
<field name="ocr">j4jJ ivp a  pj a K a  1 vw1 Iq Ii 41 jI 4 p wiqi 9 x 4 mK hA 1i I b Air h1hh m  Wrd I iP  w hkbgI K pu A  U EUi ft w x   r EVWV r z  EL I Li ry Li  iA IA Ij r1rL IA 4 7  I7d cw ind pp I   iL m  Ei Ii Em  V6 W TA  ws 7k 41J P4j rILb F bJ Ii L EW ITT 43 LY I hf i p j hP 2 kU 3 p  L  L I jAw 4J 4J L VJ m  LZ A1 41 ly  14 I  war UIb7bIW LJ pu II W L1 vY up I I iTi pp yd id t Ema E2 p  ow F Fwrqb a  1q I akjl I  VEIV pri A WE 4 </field>
</doc>
</add>
