<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">8833</field>
<field name="name">HVC426050</field>
<field name="asr">music noise as much as you might not want to think about it you may find yourself in a situation where you have to change a tire by yourself noise the good news is breath your owner's manual has very easy to follow instructions noise long before you might have to tackle this gap noise make sure you know where to find the spare tire noise that will ranch also called the tired and the jack noise if you experience of flat pull off the road into an area that is safe harding and as level as possible noise once you stop to think that the vehicle for moving but the gear shift in part if you have an automatic transmission noise or in first to reverse if you have a manual transmission noise packing stopped the vehicle or can turn on the hazard lights are receptive your ship noise apply parking brake and removed the keys to meet mission noise the canal out passenger streaming in india noise to be even more certain that the vehicle while not no noise you should put blacks at the front where the tire farthest away from the one being changed noise that would be the tire on the other side at the opposite in the vehicle noise now brandy a floor mat uses a meal and pat noise teacher will already have done a run for the past you know exactly where to find everything noise before you left the car with that jack noise while the weight of the vehicle is still on it noise it was in the light and that's noise this keeps the wheel from turning into force what next moves noise depending on the style of your vehicle you may have to removal will cover first noise gerry all unmet slapped the since then noise turning them right tightens up so just remember left this los white is tight noise raising the vehicle with the jack in the wrong position can damage the fear i even make a car noise to help hold like personal injury can be a family noise be sure to fit the jacqueline packed into the proper location before raising him noise never get on the idea for me to supported only by a jack noise you're owner's manual and have the specific location where to place the gap noise can you get cannot clockwise to raise to be it noise recent far enough off the ground noise for the spare tire to fit underneath the will live noise we'll allow real nuts and take up a flat tire noise remove any roster there from the willed walls mounting surfaced and spare tire noise the places they're tire on the wheel mounting surface noise what a_lot that's back on with around it in half and not toward the wheel remember right is tight noise to try and_then towards the right i am and just enough to make sure there's not noise if you try to tighten more than we'll we'll spend noise when the mets are on the luntz securely slowly lowered that jack noise once the vehicles pull weight is on the spare tighten lug nuts following in this class pattern until all the knots are fully security noise now put you tolls and_then back where they belong in stature flat noise i'll be instructions and the owner's manual for proper storage of the tools that can fight the fire noise it's really important to take the vehicle to the nearest can dealer's service station and says you can't noise they have been that's tight with a fork range to the proper specifications noise mr. lynch can also tell you what your tire can be fixed or if you need a new one noise if you need an entire i've trained g. m. technician can help you determine which brand and moll is right for you noise a member noise many g. m. dealers now sell tires in the end of best qualified experts on replacement tires for g. m. vehicles noise keep your tires attack operating condition noise and to get the proper new tires many need them to see mr. goodman and one of the new seven thousand g. m. dealers nationwide </field>
<field name="ocr">1 i 4 vj7 d  Ca 77A9A 779A 7dA9A 14i 479J 14i 779J 479J 77A  7i7A ii 7i7A ii 7i7A ii 7i7A ii 7i7A ii 7i7A ii 4 F7uIq   Zif7 ZZ7 Ff p7W F z pr F z pp I p F7A ii 7K 7A ZA FA FA 7K IA IA PIP  PIP pplr pplr A E7 ppp  p77K 27N 2N F 1 Y w A w a p z W A I 7i4 TA P7 Lz rii F  74 74 AE zzz zIz AT1 F t t  1  r  L7 1  Tti iL  ii   r  mL gz p h I 5 IL IL  4 if 1 f  I L VA FL b A IAl ffi bh jv rf 1i2 ppi ff t aiIb rzri rzri p  I   a 1 f I F7f 7 L I f  F I  7A 1 5f kiu if IF I V 7 Jv I  jv F I  7 j  k 1 PAiL IL I I 1f i4  1 1f 1 1 9 I WA  WA  Ip F J Wa Er 44 Pp w   I bA Li Li iL mdm  FTA v Fq md ad b lAw  jw s Ju F w  7 IU Ii II2i I 7 p5 2 7 wJ I ib hr 1 7 U  2 w 4 A  vf vv ii 1  I I 7 F 5 I y I k4 iri pp Ybb pI F P7  7 4 zIIz r  rr        2 U WE U U wL wL j B U    U  U  U A   U       j j j 4 im U J 4I rn  m  m U    U  U  U 7       1   1 7Tf 2A  4 77K  I 7A 9 jj 9  EEL  4i   A  7  me pr  pr  Ac pP  F  F  V Frz U </field>
</doc>
</add>
