<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">8947</field>
<field name="name">HVC477726</field>
<field name="asr">we run inside your enemy in iraq to see it noise these are noise are are used today noise he is waiting right wrist is granted but noise with health care noise yeah noise and they char noise and salt and pepper and a little bit of butter noise and that's okay noise the first lady as_a c. d. e. a. can i make all of this century the rep bread like this noise and in a cup works really well because the yellow outfits rain there and it allows the white of the eight to spread on the telephone bread noise and i just either one side of bread noise and that's the side that's going to be signed on noise in the frying pan at the beginning noise yeah noise because they're going_to put butter in the franking noise and make sure you do start at the little desk that's always the kid's favorite noise is the middle desk because they can noise so the i. n. which is better key frying pan music at around a_little bit music fred you better so i don't know music and don't forget to vote yes music and then you break the edge right in the middle of the wholesome you_know goes in the hole and the white scratches music and the death squads music then take a little bit assaults and its assault on it that course and_that noise like noise so what time it would have run ads noise yeah noise and you don't come out now to depends on how you might hear and if you like it or not he said it's either and that's it noise but are they are and you can write and they're fairly far outside on boats noise still the lead in that range their hand on the other side and then all of this noise and for the middle just covers long noise music noise music noise really really helping craft this that if there is pain noise noise you know if i asked him why noise but the key is to you noise getting a half brother or a small teams costs make holes in it be your chest business centers of the way it is for it right noise the west in a sense here by asking whether the ground noise as i left to save the nation noise just put it on a plate and okay at a desk and acts in the in sausages for it would be to help your part noise and hey no service here noise but the great you've got a wonderfully healthy right music o. k. music noise </field>
<field name="ocr">AC  AC  UDq  I  4 jail rfl V K a k r ku w 4 uIn HIP pr iii pr EI pr NJ 6 9 U1U  I SW IL gi  IL I I S pr 1 NJ Iii II I 6I 91 nm LJ pr rr 5 L I pr IA pr LI I fJ ph IbI Lf 1 S 9 L f uIJ L1 6 j 7 mr S 01 LL I fJ bb I Lm MI 301 I  fXJ 1j iI mI q  k1 0  L4 ppy1 Ii p1 1 A 4J U ml ry mu dI w1 L Ewe VaLJ yin I  IL r 1 r  7 p B ww  A A MI As MI IIhii C rni F IF iJ 1 WA LJ iN 7j ma t I lb El IL I U mWYAi V1YAI1 d FwpF F J mJ NA  wyji 4 d4 Tj zJ v qLW ILJ em diaJ 4 LTd hiL4 LU V  p mm   Iib k IF 1 8q1 m7 4 1 I 4 A5 dii I 11P1 I V  L7 7 4 xr  I1 A bid myi  I 7 YEll I k am IL LAI hI mud I 11L4 4  LI Ni4 w A 6 pwz 1  I A 1 I w EL I1 Ij z  V rj pY Ij wrb 4i 1u en 2 ig hL II 4b a bce em j2 rAV ILl I AJ WJ41 Al A ii I E I Th p I W wq41 LI I I EL EL El K 4  tw EIq Eu U iI h I L K I Pr um priyj 1 F IL 5 iq ii IJ 4m   t I  WI  qv hNI UEbiIEIhl 7  gut a gS IY Iv EL S 1 7Wjj Er a U  I U L4L J L E I I LL  I p 114 Z4 I 4 19q II iLl Li V  ru 1 I7T 14 AU LI 44 IT 1I uu Y vz iL 1 LI L7i ill 4 EhIIY LW1 IY IsbI I ru wJ V a b Al  u ii  L J q L1 d r A aI b 41 s1II  S  SE  S  w we iA I  Ubb I S A F S   t I  U  Iqmh v i IL WI KU a  IK BY I  w I A rr r1r VA w11   I L1 WE I ri 4 F  e  4  WI 1 W1A 4 A LL Li ii Pr dL L Ai EL uIp EL W I I  II El U rzu I1 Xj LIZ U TiN 1mm KIWI TEN IW ml U I I L5 p I7U I   pp Ij uI IAAL TA p   u IILI AU Ii I 0I 1 p p psi F IT  1 iir  I1 rir w1 SW rtr  w  1U F wI 9 A4 Th a r gin i 1 dl EL LI 7U 6 6 diN EI Ia e e I 9 xI ILl Ni I II  XI XI hA N II j4 m I 1V amdAA 4 Aa E F hv hF U di 5J U 2  p 1 2  SW L  pU i 4I ar A  1s  w aEl 5 III IE 4 11W ea4  Irq vYwI 1q rA2 iIU L  ii ff 911 rr   i E  I A kt J74 a Uf 1 dv rA vv WV rd q hEY Ta qEJ rw Jx pIpp xu rp 1 tI Mi ri KAI L LL Lb IbII Lb Ii pr4q L rA2  YY rA IC Ti Ii KI Lii F rA rA LIaT LL U K7 4K rj Jp TI EJ rA2 vi w11q IAiI I2 Ii  L2 L1 V Zi7 L E L7A57  Al Al IWI dl ai KI Eu  bL A W w ii U1 K W aw qEmilli  two EW U an inIwu4 1g I Ahd w  F Z7C J5D WAJ JP j5T WmA pp C WA lk Lii 4 61 ml Jk TI WA kid pill rwi q  7IU IffiIE I EU fdA7ff7i LAlLa 7T IL ItI L7T E  EL LT El U mimi I U1 I  9 Al VI LJ IA L4VI I PIP 9 Wi wf ppp I Ab Ad p Fiji U rd LY 1 hi Lt im mgVIj 27h WP w Isv r  mwr liLa hilL I Lfl i4 LI LL xi I II 1 r4q  a WA em LAy bb 4 U w uq I 4 L JDJ I n id4II  1E1 IfI I i I I Er I J L  ra ml a  I 1 I I </field>
</doc>
</add>
