<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">908</field>
<field name="name">HVC1743</field>
<field name="asr">noise welcome to linguists sticks a tool for studying human language noise but in this wrecked which in in filler noise i_am your instructor from this course noise breath and_to be a little bit about myself noise and so noise oh but about filler my restriction when i've done noise and a little bit about when we're sticks noise interest to do you started on thinking about noise the content of the course noise like training is a linguist dick so that a p. h. d. from the university of washington i studied cycling with sticks noise in particular i think i did experiments of studying people's brain waves in response to noise word to non works noise i also have training in noise filler communication disorders so noise i'm sorry noise filler speech when which couple interest noise clinically breath in the past noise i've worked with special needs children noise a population zero to three noise eventually breath so i'm interested not only in the noise theoretical aspects of linguistics which will be looking at in this course but also the practical noise applied noise aspects of linguistics in the way is that noise can inform us in understanding how people grow noise noise i just want point out that linguist x. is really a huge field noise it could talk to some really pretty much everything noise let us to do and being human noise and so there's a_lot of room within the breast x. noise for finding something that you're interested in noise filler so i hope that you will discover noise when we're stick noise aspects too noise filler breath your interests and be able to noise explore them follow up on that in this course noise o. k. noise that's it for now welcome could come to lessons and to noise i'll tell you a_little bit about the books that were using noise in this course </field>
<field name="ocr">EL p 15  lET XI ii pr pp 2I iI PT pr XI  I 9 rI 25 pE rna FE xl rI1 iht j 1  I Ii FL tF L 1 </field>
</doc>
</add>
