<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">9282</field>
<field name="name">HVC617211</field>
<field name="asr">noise breath gas wages are designed to operate on natural or l. p. gap noise breath the two major differences between natural and l. p. gas breath are the b. t. u. rating per cubic foot breath and the weight or density of the gat noise natural gas is rated around one thousand b. t. u. were cubic foot breath and this happens heavy is there noise l. p. is rated at three thousand b. t. u. or cubic foot breath and it's twice as heavy as they're noise breath filler the majority of the gas ranges solar installed on natural gas lines breath the rangers are shipped from the factories adjusted for natural gas noise two converted gas range from natural to well p. breath it is necessary to convert the pressure regulator breath heighten the spot breath or a share breath and_it just the air on the other burner or burner noise if the top burners our standard burners quite looks but until it sleeps and adjust the air noise breath if the top earners are shield burners breath it will be necessary to install and help each hit noise breath this kid will have replacement or possess restricted as chokes breath and the installation instructions noise breath well breath that by step procedure consult the installation instructions with the range breath and the instructions with the kit noise breath they'll be gaskins delivered an expanded pressure of eleven inches water column noise because natural gas is not deliver that is standard pressure breath but pressure regulator is installed on each gas range noise the regulator is designed to reduce and maintain upward pressure under flow breath of four inches within incoming gas pressure breath of four and a half to four teenagers with natural gas breath and in output of ten inches within input of eleven inches on l. p. noise breath the gas should apply is connected to the pressure regulator noise breath the gas leave the pressure regulator true wanted to output too noise breath one to be connected to the man of all which supplies gas to the top burner noise breath the other two disconnected to the other does well noise breath that section of the regulator that is connected to the other valve has an annual shut off twelve breath which allows the gas to the envelope of the show at all noise breath the man of all this journey of gas to the top burner about noise two types of top burner gas wells were used breath and are identified by the number of degrees there shafts will turn noise breath one hundred ten degrees breath or a two hundred ten degree noise breath the one hundred ten degree vow this turn noise all along to light the burner breath then back toward the off position to adjust the flame height noise breath the two hundred ten degree val has a light position around eighty degrees breath noise and then turned toward the talked with just a plain white noise breath the two hundred ten degree valve also has a minimum planned job hunt through this breath i understand noise breath at the end of the valve war at the end of the tubing attached of about breath is that it sure of it breath or breath but with an orchestra inside breath they controlled the maximum amount of gas to the burner noise breath if the valve has a breath but there is a mixture pin inside breath that allows the orchestra in this but with the adjustable noise breath to reduce the maximum gas will or will it just before o. p. breath the study striking against picture pit noise breath as the gasoline new yorkers breath it is injected into the burner noise as the gas passes into the burner breath the year that passes through is drawn into and mixed with began noise is there is called the primary here noise the year and gas makes you then passes through the murder breath and out the burner port source slots noise breath as the gas here mixture passes through the port just laws breath additional air surrounding the burnett is drawn into the mixture noise breath the shared drawn into the mixture outside the burner is called secondary here noise </field>
<field name="ocr">ThUD1I IA ThUD1I ThUD1I ThUD1I ThUD1I ThUD1I ThUD1I ThUD1I A ThUD1I Y I A A El El El El El El El El El LI  LI  LI  LI  LI  LI  R  LI  II RIMAR PRIMARY ww ww ww ww ww ww ww ww ww ww ww ww ww ww ww ww ww ww ww ww PRIMARY WEIGHT 10 Output II Input 10 Output II Input 10 Output II Input 10 Output II Input 10 Output II Input 10 Output II Input go Output 7Mm 7uwmi 7uwmi 7uwmi 7uwmi 7uwmi 7uwmi 7uwmi puwmi puwmi 7u 7u 7u 7u 7u 7u 7u 7u 7u 7u 7u 7u 7u 7u 7u 7u 7u 7u mm 0W e    A  I sk hJ hJ hJ hJ hJ I sk I sk I sk I sk F U Pt ppzd LI lrmwmw lrmwmw mnmw Irtmnmw wmntmw wmnw L imnmw L imnmw L L L L mnmw L mnmw L imwmw L L p  lrmnunv 0  lrmnunv 0  lrmnunv 0  Irmnunv Irmnunv 0  unv Irmnunv unv Irmnunv unv Irmnunv Irmnunv unv Irmnunv unv Irmnunv Irmnunv Irmnunv Irmnunv limnuiw ThUD1I ThUD1I ThUD1I IA ThUD1I UI ThUD1I ThUD1I ThUD1I IA PRIMARY PRIMARY PRIMARY PRIMARY PRIMARY PRIMARY PRIMARY RMAR vnnTrny PRIMARY PRIMARY PRIMARY PRIMARY PRIMARY PRIMARY PRIMARY PRIMARY PRIMARY PRIMARY H P3OdN NATURAL NATURAL IQMflW NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL itqusnw NATURAL Lqnno IIQWREOPMMU NATURALGM NATURALGAS LlAfUZPffMU NATURAL LINflIDF3OPM NATURAL LImfltDPUCPM NATURAL uqmnwPOPMU NATURAL uqmnwPOPMU uqmnwPOPANI NATURAL uqmnwPOPANI NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL 4LIqmflw POPM6 NATURAL uqmnto POPM6 NATURAL uqmnto NATURAL uqmnto NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL tIWFtIflftOPMU NATURAL tIWFtIflPOPMU NATURAL tIWFtIflPOPMU NATURAL tIWFtIflPOPMU NATURAL tIWFtIflPOPMU NATURAL tIWFtIflPOPMU NATURAL tIWFtIflPOPMU NATURAL tIWFtIflPOPMU NATURAL tIWFtIflPOPMU NATURAL tIWFtIflPOPMU NATURAL tIWFtIflPOPMU NATURAL tIWFtIflPOPMU NATURAL UQWFtIDPOPMU NATURAL UQWFtIDPOPMU NATURAL UQWFtIDPOPMU NATURAL UQWFtIDPOPMU NATURAL UQWFtIDPOPMU NATURAL UQWFtIDPOPMU NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL NATURAL WEIG NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT QNAhD NATURAL WEIGHT QNAhD NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL QwAEO WEIGHT NATURAL QwAEO WEIGHT NATURAL QwAEO WEIGHT NATURAL QwAEO WEIGHT NATURAL QwAEO WEIGHT NATURAL QwAEO WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL QwAEO WEIGHT NATURAL QwAEO WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL QwAEO WEIGHT NATURAL QwAEO WEIGHT NATURAL QwAEO WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT I fiX NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT I 2X NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT I 12X NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT I 12X NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT I 12X NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT 1000 WEIGHT NAURAL I000 WEIGHT NAURAL I000 WEIGHT NAURAL I000 WEIGHT NAURAL I000 WEIGHT NAURAL I000 WEIGHT NAURAL I000 NAURAL I000 WEIGHT NAURAL I000 WEIGHT NAURAL I000 WEIGHT NAURAL I000 WEIGHT NAURAL I000 WEIGHT NAURAL I000 WEIGHT NAURAL I000 WEIGHT NATURAL I000 WEIGHT NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL 1000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL l000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT lax NATURAL I000 WEIGHT I fiX NATURAL I000 Ii Zaid p7j IIj q r  1 El IAAS ISA S AAU ISA S AlAS AAFAa lAg AArAA IAA IAAS ISAS U SW ASAI IdA S AdA S ISA S IAS mMa AArU ISA S AAI AlA S IA ISA S ISA S ASAJ ftirAA aiitA SrA IAr S JIArLtI ISA I IArA  IArA  IUn mm Un ut NATURAL GAS NATURAL GAS NATURAL GAS NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS NATURAL GAS NATURAL GAS NATURAL GAS NATURAL GAS NATURAL GAS NATURAL GAS NATURAL GAS NATURAL GAS NATURAL GAS NATURAL GAS NATURAL GAS InpLt NATURAL GAS 4 1121 ITa r 400 Output NATURAL GAS 400 Output NATURAL GAS 400 Output NATURAL GAS 400 Output NATURAL GAS 400 Output NATURAL GAS 400 Output NATURAL GAS 400 Output NATURAL GAS 400 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4 Output NATURAL GAS 4g Output Input NATURAL GAS 47OMast NATURAL GAS NATURt GAS II Input II Input II Input II Input II Input II Input II Input JO Output II Input Jo Output II Input Jo Output II Input Jo Output II Input Jo Output II Input Jo Output II Input Jo Output II Input Jo Output II Input Jo Output II Input Jo Output II Input Jo Output log Output log Output log Output log Output log Output log Output log Output log Output log Output log Output log Output log Output log Output log Output log Output log Output log Output II Input 10 Output II Input IO Output II Input II Input II Input to Output IIinput to Output IIinput to Output IIinput to Output II Input to Output II Input to Output II Input to Output II Input to Output II Input LI H LI H LI H LI H LI H LI uJIuuiw PINAY AIR   dUJ  PmMARY  PmMARY  PmMARY  PmMARY  PmMARY  PmMARY  PmMARY  PmMARY  PmMARY  PmMARY  PmMARY  PmMARY  PmMARY  PmMARY L PRIMARY  PmMARY  PmMARY SECONDARY ECONDARY SECONDARY SECONDARY SECONDARY SECONDARY SECONDARY 4k u SECONDARY SECONDARY SECONDARY SECONDARY SECONDARY SECONDARY SECONDARY SECONDARY SECONDARY SECONDARY SECONDARY SECONDARY Jd INAfl1 </field>
</doc>
</add>
