<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">9380</field>
<field name="name">HVC669772</field>
<field name="asr">noise breath yeah noise music noise music breath the other one music noise music i think you're okay i take care of noise okay noise breath mhm noise mhm noise music noise o. k. noise noise noise noise music yeah noise music noise music noise music noise music noise music noise music noise yeah noise music noise mr. perot noise this week noise music noise music noise music noise music noise music noise music yeah music noise music noise music noise music noise we'll get it right noise </field>
<field name="ocr">W09 2009 ii LUJ 200 OO9 LOW Low I 4 2009 2009 4 2009 2009 2009 Low Low I 4 OO9 4 I 4 2009  4 2009 Low  I 2009 Low OO9 S TI U bi 2009 LOW 2009 LOW 2009 U b 2009 rr irch Our 200 U hi 2009 LOW 2009 ILL 2009 one S  2 I U  4   4   WI p 4J wqq7 rnIiI I 4 Im 171 il   94 4      P s biJ 4    h  4 a       mEwu      j    j   Ihb   hbL1 Vq1W   hLl K Imp rJ Li a   L z   L z iIm   L z   iIE 4A iU Pm WL tffJ k T WT L a k f VI I  Im  Im  Im  mu   7 I  Im  Fri Im    LW 0I Im  Im  Im  w SW  r w mu w w mu 1w mum  hL q mm   s mum   sQ 7 v mu w I t 7  1w  7 b Im   7 b mum   V      mum  mum   mum    M LU 1w 1w  I Sw L7 9 J Lu 9 J SEP  SEP  U  bJ    4  F L I 2  ui  mu  F 47 mu i p1 iJ w  w a 7 I w  w  mm   h w  L1 Ws s1 p tLL Jul  1 II  I Uij rI L1 IEE 71 U  tp   A ii 9  9  U    LWI    C K EU L    pmE V I a1m  h    a   C   C   C my LA hUb nA  Etir pM p4  9 1    yv  ia 0 KJ  jeb lj PAh   p ys 4 wAMi bLWI tg S sII t I b uah7  1 1 I  hu hu v WIWL  YIj  st  C iiW    b IU IU II V F4 s  ft 1 jh  IhJ 4b hAAV  Li  IJ U LI i  r   LA WK Z2    LZL YQ  1   fe  e  e  IJI V U a  4 4   bL  1   I  I  0Sq  I N  p y  5  p S 9 9 mA  9 9 9 9  d U 17 7d Ii I I W I C 71I   Ij F1I   t   iw mpI 3I 4 9I i ih D  p  p b 71 7i J I jI kaJi IL    1p  p    q 4 zJU I I A1 71 6  7j   SV  PL 1 1 V z  4 WV  r C U   WV t4 Zp t4 Zp 4Uh  Fr ft F U I E  2 Ii YL 4 L hk V KIK F a   I 4 1  PA FZW2 WW K  A  ma wrJj in wr I up AY U W iaIp I I U Kb  hi iL4 X4 14q  uz a7J iu I 1f 1f LN MI   U U miI L4 1 FTI 4j p I  v w4 dwrs dwrs liY V iIv Lah I P1 171   Lid 4 1h 1 E 7 7 V q F 9  A pv h L ril   atmfltv V 4 KhWd4w I I LJjJ Lr flJ 4 qc 9  r 9  r iI 9  9 9 9  9  9  9 9  my IU   4 V jay f r f t qj 4 rr Tdr LI A N J   r7 r71 kXWI V tra r  r r J b  xw ALWJ 3 r   e  x   IIJ EP7 1k gtiaI dm1   p I IF kI irs  I A iLU A4J Ut t  I MUAt u 1LZid U 4 LIIIW 1 4 itt 4i LU bJd wp q2sb rr  1WNb  w w  0 7pL AAA r Ia It a V  7  A wr r  ew I  eY IAM 1l F ala K1LA eaW 4 4 61 w3 upI hi xu 4 4mb 7 ct    rn7KZ6 r7 IF Is 17 9IftP qmm1 I d4 rqv Ih L I   4V bq F Li LT3Tj mrN         w      tI L F iI   Yw  A o p F JI I 2 ILL </field>
</doc>
</add>
