<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">9443</field>
<field name="name">HVC699015</field>
<field name="asr">noise noise noise the word yeah noise noise noise yeah noise the eleventh breath noise noise noise noise breath filler yeah i may noise mhm noise breath noise yeah breath noise you mean you know filler breath were linked to whom breath noise you didn't like what i'll donate their workers noise o. k. l. m. noise do they live like that noise well two hundred is on the west noise but that if you don't want to_know what i'm noise noise yeah well noise i think noise what a noise and that is another factor is there a one armed determined it was punching these forms noise joe noise noise noise well noise all right noise but the problem noise all right noise why then did you know bruce and you know noise what's not breath when the world know that noise but at that time breath they move up to him honey and then to put your hand down here so don't come up that i mean they're little noise yeah sure i'm just down there just are you noise there you go noise you call that well yeah i've got a big filler noise and i'm sure and won't hurt you_know i think noise noise okay noise thank you noise noise think there probably is tied my hands with the mind of what the point we don't breath well noise what noise noise well o. k. move northward breath okay noise </field>
<field name="ocr">I yr r1i FNU NE 9NU I Eu A1Y 1J 71  11W 4q jPUPI  II qppr p 1 qI LV k I  Uhi  Wi LL KU iI I 45 P3 IA ZFAA4I 4 F I    tKI J1i 2fr U rW wd Jzj TVN K1 IJ I 4J IL wT KI aL iKI LA7  I1b wr If WvV  LR 1 IL 11 kjE I  U A  U KY  L rrr p WSmmrm 1A1 A  I  iii bP T Ii1 L4j Yj i  il 1dId AI tY rr 4 LII h1I7T 5 L1 Ti iIIJ LW Li A I IA p kH1 LK1 IIMN LJ IhL IA N I  11 TVI rde tJ IbNh wr 7a 1h 1T La jY w U E p a m I tLt  LJtA f 121 JCL I hE Will ii F L21 L I a A I dl L4 Iw  N  F rNmII p SI U smcj ETIdCJ sricj flICA mc Er   a r1 vw  q  hO WPv 4 1   e dL CARE CA pi rc CARE CARE IARE ICA ICE ICAE ICARE LYb 1 CAI L1r4 LJ 1E L 1 II 4u Er  a Kr4 4I 1  I wa md zA wY I N IhLi Pr sari Lw zJ aj Y N LU L I U  r  mab a a Ah iJ 1 IcqI IL k  ni vS  ji I CiI 1i hEuVrJ 1I I  j7F   wpl i  FJ wr 4U I EAA V AJ Mr sib It Jp U1 a rL wII1I LJ ml if  r I iI 4U  7Y 1 4 YY I ii qra1 vbvr 4 bJ1 rAP Wv I WA ji U  mk P a 1 IiE q  LUAI FILl 74Yi LJJ pii VJ WI 4 a U V w r LJ 71 Eli 1r w a 5I XA 1 WE MtI I  LLF LL 4 3hm p1  LJ FA L  0 KJJLJ tj U  I A bii pgJ 7j alL 21 U  IML F1 hi  24 MU WE All 7j U b v4AbrpJ kL TJ I  aF Erw EgN Wi vYj LEr L  tfr LA wv LPI UN14kMl U Y r4U dj Lqw   Pr p k J ikI ardd 1  v4 4dv1 qi 7 J F  AJ iI ii A iir j4P q p A I K iiA a j I In ml VTQa Fm E  K F ai aA 15 ii 1 r m  xv1 F7 jth LEA ri 1 2iS VA KI kA Lq IL U BaF zKI 4g1 IK hmbL  3 vFpmw W176 LL N </field>
</doc>
</add>
