<add>
<doc>
<field name="id">9534</field>
<field name="name">HVC741067</field>
<field name="asr">well yeah noise well i didn't know did yeah noise now what will be able to go noise you know her noise i will not lead noise noise noise and filler breath well who noise they will will lead lawyer how would they get you out of our news noise yeah noise they don't really have a core smile and the i. r. a. and just filler they can use the word where there's a penny next exiled although well were you allowed to whatever works noise well no you don't do that noise all they're going to do it is noise little happened there weren't this for years noise what happened noise he just walked back to the world noise and they didn't believe her noise you bet your life noise the cold weather noise when you come back noise and they're cool noise objection noise noise noise so isn't there noise you want that noise the elected not you know it's not that you know a lot on the attack noise the word breath lot_of that she'll she'll be quantities in haiti that is a whole noise filler breath you just say that caller noise well yeah noise well i didn't know did yeah noise now what will be able to go noise you know her noise i will not lead noise noise noise and filler breath well who noise they will will lead lawyer how would they get you out of our news noise yeah noise they don't really have a core smile and the i. r. a. and just filler they can use the word where there's a penny next exiled although well were you allowed to whatever works noise well no you don't do that noise all they're going to do it is noise little happened there weren't this for years noise what happened noise he just walked back to the world noise and they didn't believe her noise you bet your life noise the cold weather noise when you come back noise and they're cool noise objection noise noise noise so isn't there noise you want that noise the elected not you know it's not that you know a lot on the attack noise the word breath lot_of that she'll she'll be quantities in haiti that is a whole noise filler breath you just say that caller noise and they breath well filler filler noise well yeah noise well i didn't know did yeah noise now what will be able to go noise you know her noise i will not lead noise noise noise and filler breath well who noise they will will lead lawyer how would they get you out of our news noise yeah noise they don't really have a core smile and the i. r. a. and just filler they can use the word where there's a penny next exiled although well were you allowed to whatever works noise well no you don't do that noise all they're going to do it is noise little happened there weren't this for years noise what happened noise he just walked back to the world noise and they didn't believe her noise you bet your life noise the cold weather noise when you come back noise and they're cool noise objection noise noise noise so isn't there noise you want that noise the elected not you know it's not that you know a lot on the attack noise the word breath lot_of that she'll she'll be quantities in haiti that is a whole noise filler breath you just say that caller noise and they breath well filler filler noise we're very old basically there's almost no ma'am noise and why don't you noise the show you how do these things or unknown right_now to look like a whole lot noise but that would leave yourself here let me filler breath that noise noise noise did noise noise and what and what did she got what you're alive yeah noise but we will slide noise well yeah noise well i didn't know did yeah noise now what will be able to go noise you know her noise i will not lead noise noise noise and filler breath well who noise they will will lead lawyer how would they get you out of our news noise yeah noise they don't really have a core smile and the i. r. a. and just filler they can use the word where there's a penny next exiled although well were you allowed to whatever works noise well no you don't do that noise all they're going to do it is noise little happened there weren't this for years noise what happened noise he just walked back to the world noise and they didn't believe her noise you bet your life noise the cold weather noise when you come back noise and they're cool noise objection noise noise noise so isn't there noise you want that noise the elected not you know it's not that you know a lot on the attack noise the word breath lot_of that she'll she'll be quantities in haiti that is a whole noise filler breath you just say that caller noise and they breath well filler filler noise we're very old basically there's almost no ma'am noise and why don't you noise the show you how do these things or unknown right_now to look like a whole lot noise but that would leave yourself here let me filler breath that noise noise noise did noise noise and what and what did she got what you're alive yeah noise but we will slide noise and i'm thinking on the show well i've got a whole clean used to be it noise well yeah noise well i didn't know did yeah noise now what will be able to go noise you know her noise i will not lead noise noise noise and filler breath well who noise they will will lead lawyer how would they get you out of our news noise yeah noise they don't really have a core smile and the i. r. a. and just filler they can use the word where there's a penny next exiled although well were you allowed to whatever works noise well no you don't do that noise all they're going to do it is noise little happened there weren't this for years noise what happened noise he just walked back to the world noise and they didn't believe her noise you bet your life noise the cold weather noise when you come back noise and they're cool noise objection noise noise noise so isn't there noise you want that noise the elected not you know it's not that you know a lot on the attack noise the word breath lot_of that she'll she'll be quantities in haiti that is a whole noise filler breath you just say that caller noise and they breath well filler filler noise we're very old basically there's almost no ma'am noise and why don't you noise well yeah noise well i didn't know did yeah noise now what will be able to go noise you know her noise i will not lead noise noise noise and filler breath well who noise they will will lead lawyer how would they get you out of our news noise yeah noise they don't really have a core smile and the i. r. a. and just filler they can use the word where there's a penny next exiled although well were you allowed to whatever works noise well no you don't do that noise all they're going to do it is noise little happened there weren't this for years noise what happened noise he just walked back to the world noise and they didn't believe her noise you bet your life noise the cold weather noise when you come back noise and they're cool noise objection noise noise noise so isn't there noise you want that noise the elected not you know it's not that you know a lot on the attack noise the word breath lot_of that she'll she'll be quantities in haiti that is a whole noise filler breath you just say that caller noise and they breath well filler filler noise we're very old basically there's almost no ma'am noise and why don't you noise the show you how do these things or unknown right_now to look like a whole lot noise but that would leave yourself here let me filler breath that noise noise noise did noise noise and what and what did she got what you're alive yeah noise but we will slide noise and i'm thinking on the show well i've got a whole clean used to be it noise it was an appropriate and if one were to get their hands in haiti and filler it would_be just used the april allowed all media back in the shadows of the tree noise well what do you know we hear noise why do you have to make people who care breath filler right right and what are called for his model whatever cruised the turkish war who christian yes they were more breath when the plane left noise hold it noise noise you didn't do well breath filler i mean you know noise and i'll tell you what do you believe that what he's doing noise she didn't think that while he didn't like filler you know noise i remember it noise the real stuff of profit and you can do a number that he didn't solve it noise you can use that as well breath you will will try to do filler breath and though many have called whatever noise after breath the leaders of the war noise breath well breath noise good noise to profit and i'll tell you that he didn't get a lawyer noise oh no noise probably yes noise you did your grandmother for christmas and all the time that that noise and you do grandparents whatever shut it down filler filler quite a_lot of the filler filler noise he knew then what noise with that with the trial and get you there noise we're going to hear actually you know mother whatever yeah just unbelievable swell noise working for him now noise and filler i'm willing to clean that up noise it would mean and what did you talk you know that noise i appreciate it was all put private i would use to show you noise there is nothing for cubans to be sure breath well filler oh noise thank you_to do with what works noise and you know noise the year after that i don't really know what they thought that is that noise the classes will or will it noise </field>
<field name="ocr">Ii il a AM I U iq rYw WL I sv IL LI 1 L12 1I AJ V AJ I mk h md ww ii dd E W7 I t p p pr L  U p   Iii iii 4q Wa IIy  I w1 t1 L ha 4 U 7 p P JLi 4 K I JA AU L bEL U  W y 4 ww 1w vq 7I 7 I I rn Y 7 I4 S I i1 wiL I1 Lr h  I 2V p A Es WV I Jr I I pI rp r m1 7 I w I 7 LW b L rZI 1 kI IL   jr IfII a a jli ILI ILI JuJ Sf iJqI iJqI LJ LJ LJ LJ LJ LJ 2d 2d 2d 2d IllTI AlL 1 1I rz 2 U I  1Ev pw vlw U b ELAN  IMd hh k S p u WV Bh I 4d I I a I q P I p  1 ii 1w ij j7pw E Iru p  Aw i ij k 4 rn r p LId iii uij V i LLJ pii B rn LiI3 ii  1 rL F PAl 7U wv hJ Ew pw jEWtm v11 LL L7 Ad ri N1 Ld Ld A ILd iLd iLd ii U L A IA IA Fri EU flu JI5J  4 5Ii Er Er Er Er Er iLd 4J Iai my W  RF gp ppa 3Ii ii ILd ILd ppp K  a  iI rn arp 1W mi A  U g1 wi py 9 py ILd LId ILd uq iId iId A1i  a j iLd WAU iI 1 AU Mv 1 1A hr YIP LiY ArJ MIt r9N Aid iI r 14U wU 1j i 3 vL Lk Dw 1 LqE B A 4j 9 EAd Kj rn F1 WV </field>
</doc>
</add>
